<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
><channel><title>Digital Marketing &#8211; CairoCorps Consulting</title> <atom:link href="https://cairocorps.com/category/digital-marketing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><link>https://cairocorps.com</link> <description>Creations &#124; Digital Transformations</description> <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 10:31:14 +0000</lastBuildDate> <language>en-US</language> <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod> <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency><image> <url>https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/ccc-logo-1.png?fit=25%2C32&#038;ssl=1</url><title>Digital Marketing &#8211; CairoCorps Consulting</title><link>https://cairocorps.com</link> <width>32</width> <height>32</height> </image> <site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">142080933</site> <item><title>Why Digital Marketing is Important in 2018?</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 07:27:48 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO agency in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[seo company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5185</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Why digital marketing is important in 2018? Marketing is the backbone of every business in the world without marketing you never succeed in your respective business. Marketing is how you sell a product when customers need the explanation of awesome products. The present reality is that promoting sales at the intersection of the business, therefore, [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/">Why Digital Marketing is Important in 2018?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="wp-image-5186 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important.png?resize=594%2C334&#038;ssl=1" alt="why digital marketing is important" width="594" height="334" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 594px) 100vw, 594px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1 style="text-align: left;">Why digital marketing is important in 2018?</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">Marketing is the backbone of every business in the world without marketing you never succeed in your respective business. Marketing is how you sell a product when customers need the explanation of awesome products. The present reality is that promoting sales at the intersection of the business, therefore, the client – the good arbiter of the self-interests of the business and therefore the wants of the customer. Current days have two main marketing that includes online marketing and digital marketing. Here I write elaborately why digital marketing important in 2018. Once you read you will get more about digital marketing.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">What is Digital Marketing</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Promoting products or services or brands through several forms of digital technology that is digital marketing. For example, advertising mediums that might be used as part of the digital marketing strategy of a business could include promotional endeavors performed through the internet, social media, mobile phones, and computerized billboards. Similar to any form of marketing, the goal of digital marketing is to promote and sell a product or service. Further, the purpose of digital marketing is to connect a business or company with its target audience through several digital marketing strategies such as Search Engine Optimization(SEO), Pay Per Click(PPC), Social Media Marketing(SMM), Social Media Optimization(SMO), Newsletter Campaign and bulk SMS, and etc&#8230;</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Why digital marketing is important</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Digital marketing is most important marketing in the world because it is not only a quickly growing force in the contemporary marketing playing area but also it is set to be the future of every business, and it appears probable that digital marketing will quickly replace all types of offline marketing forms altogether because <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">advantages of digital marketing</a> is huge. While earlier generations will no doubt regret the decease of paper-based newspapers, books, communication methods, and conventional TV advertisements and radio broadcasts, those who have grown up with the internet penetration and mobile phones penetration are already covering the bright new world of digital marketing. The realities are that digital marketing methods of transmission and marketing are so fast besides cost-effective, more adaptable, efficient and modernized, so it is possibly unsurprising that once the new technology became accessible we started quickly moving into the new technology then only digital marketing so important for every business.</p><p><img class="wp-image-5187 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018.png?resize=597%2C336&#038;ssl=1" alt="" width="597" height="336" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 597px) 100vw, 597px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2>7 Important of Digital Marketing</h2><p>Here you can read seven reasons being to why digital marketing is important in 2018.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">1. The whole World Well Connected With Internet</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Why digital marketing is booming, well the whole world there are several factors associated or responsible for digital marketing growth. Besides one of the importance of digital marketing is the whole world well connected to the internet because of the cheap internet and mobile users increased. We have been seeing the difference in communication since the arrival of the internet. The Internet has undoubtedly changed the way of purchasing and communicating with the people. Everything has become the fast-paced and getting people more laziness since whatever you want just gives up at your doorstep with just one click. These are the reason for digital marketing is booming and the importance of digital marketing in 2018 and upcoming years.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">2. Customers are Online</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">People believe online as a way to cut costs and cut time. E-commerce shops assist customers of travel time and retailers of storefront costs so buyers are roaming always the internet to buy something. People rarely consider the costs that online shopping adds to their transaction. The distance between the buyer and seller adds risks to the customers plate. If youre part of an E-commerce business, the takeaway is this risks. In lightweight of this, associate degree service an e-commerce merchant will offer to ease the psychological feature prices of looking online will increase the customer’s perceived price of the merchandise. Today people are roaming the internet and customers are always online that is why digital marketing is important in 2018.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">3. Competitors are Online</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Competitors were gone beyond you in business Its sign of digital marketing adoption. Literally, most of the businesses are using digital marketing. Each year more and more businesses give up offline marketing methods and focus on SEO, Google Adwords or social media spending large money on these marketing. This is the explanation for why the market gets progressively competitive and large players to get prior to very little firms. As little business on the market, you can&#8217;t vie with them, however, there&#8217;s one thing you&#8217;ll do. you&#8217;ll use Google Alerts tool to observe your competitors. This tool can enable you to trace your competitors&#8217; product and selling methods in order that you&#8217;ll learn one thing from them and improve your own business strategy. Competitors are online so immediately hunt a best digital marketing company.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">4. Cost-effective Marketing</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">One of the importance of digital marketing is more cost-effective while comparing other offline marketing. This is especially essential for startups and small business. Digital marketing is savvier than offline marketing. This is particularly vital for independent companies as they don&#8217;t have numerous assets or a considerable measure of capital. New media can furnish you with a less expensive and more compelling publicizing digital marketing company channel. In digital marketing has many types of marketing according to your budget you can choose the suitable strategies. <img class="alignnone wp-image-5188 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/Feature_Image_Mobile_Device_Management_BYOD_Evolution.jpg?resize=630%2C295&#038;ssl=1" alt="why digital marketing is important" width="630" height="295" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/Feature_Image_Mobile_Device_Management_BYOD_Evolution.jpg?w=600&amp;ssl=1 600w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/Feature_Image_Mobile_Device_Management_BYOD_Evolution.jpg?resize=300%2C141&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 630px) 100vw, 630px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h3 style="text-align: left;">5. Cater to the Mobile Consumer</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">No doubt, Digital marketing has evolved such a lot that mobile devices are not any longer thought-about mere alternatives to private computers or laptops. Without any doubt, with the fast expansion of smartphones, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mobile_marketing" target="_blank" rel="noopener">mobile marketing</a> is the most contemporary way of data dispersal that is also today’s basic correspondence channel. Smartphones have transformed into the main part of our life that most of the grown-ups in India dependably have their mobile devices within their reaching distance. The greatest gathering of customers is using their cell phones day by day, so it&#8217;s basic that you utilize a marketing arrangement that objectives these mobile gadgets suitably.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">6. Highly Adaptable Marketing</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Importance of digital marketing is changing is that it needs digital marketers to be equally willing to vary and adapt. Flexibility, therefore, is a necessary quality during a digital promoting skilled, as a result of you usually ought to be ready to adopt new practices, update your ability set and knowledge domain, sustain with business best practices, and keep current with the newest technologies and trends. an excellent example of however things area unit perpetually dynamic in digital promoting is that the Google formula. The formula is often being updated, and each time they unharness a replacement version, it changes the means digital marketers and <a href="https://moz.com/learn/seo/what-is-seo" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEO</a> specialists approach their craft.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">7. Most of the People Shopping Online</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">A recent research has exposed that over 120 million Indian people are expected to buy the products or services through online this year. In the previous year of study exposed that as many as 108 million consumers did online shopping on mobile phones. Mobile phones are becoming the favored choice of device for e-commerce businesses. The research also highlighted a flood in the number of customers shopping on smartphones across India and the world with tier II and III cities are increasing trends.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Best Digital Marketing Company in Bangalore</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">CairoCorps Consulting is one of a best <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing company in Bangalore</a> who takes care of clients and feel their pain provide the best digital marketing of their business put their business at top of the competition despite any industry. The organization is also holding professional experts on the latest technologies of digital marketing with very comprehensive solutions.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>You have any suggestion about this blog let us know through comments&#8230;</strong></p><p><strong>More Tags:</strong> <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEO agency in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/interactive-web-solution/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing services in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/ecommerce-solutions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">e-commerce development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/mobile-application-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">e-commerce development company in Bangalore</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: left;"><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/">Why Digital Marketing is Important in 2018?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5185</post-id> </item> <item><title>How to use landing pages for your business-2018?</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 10:17:27 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category> <category><![CDATA[advantages of digital marketing]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO agency in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5085</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>How to use landing pages for your business-2018? When you are planning to create a Google AdWords for your business. The landing page is your key chance to convince the customer to convert &#8211; to buy your products, fill out a form or download a resource. You should have high-quality landing pages to optimize conversion [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/">How to use landing pages for your business-2018?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="wp-image-5086 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/how-to-use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=671%2C377&#038;ssl=1" alt="Use landing pages for business, digital marketing company in bangalore" width="671" height="377" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/how-to-use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/how-to-use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 671px) 100vw, 671px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1 style="text-align: justify;">How to use landing pages for your business-2018?</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">When you are planning to create a Google AdWords for your business. The landing page is your key chance to convince the customer to convert &#8211; to buy your products, fill out a form or download a resource. You should have high-quality landing pages to optimize conversion rates, and highly relevant pages will also lower your conversion costs.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Very important quality of an optimized landing page is relevance: Your ad text should be relevant to your keywords, your landing page should be relevant to your Google ad. Landing page with relevant ad text also gets higher quality scores and better ad rankings as a result.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Designing specific landing pages that talk directly to the user&#8217;s search query will have a real impact on your AdWords account and, most importantly, drive more conversions. It’s worth it to devote major time and effort to optimize your AdWords landing pages.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><img class="alignnone wp-image-5087 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business-410x1024.png?resize=652%2C1629&#038;ssl=1" alt="How to use landing pages for your business-2018" width="652" height="1629" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=410%2C1024&amp;ssl=1 410w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=120%2C300&amp;ssl=1 120w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=768%2C1920&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=600%2C1500&amp;ssl=1 600w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?w=800&amp;ssl=1 800w" sizes="(max-width: 652px) 100vw, 652px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Create Optimized Landing Pages for Google AdWords</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Creating AdWords landing pages can be a hard task – there’s a lot to take into consideration. Some challenges of creating AdWords landing pages include:</p><h3 style="text-align: justify;">You can’t build landing pages in AdWords:</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">You can&#8217;t have great AdWords ads for your business without solid landing pages, Google won&#8217;t provide landing page assistance within AdWords. So we need to build landing pages separately.</p><h3 style="text-align: justify;">You need outside help to make landing page:</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Designing landing pages generally <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/">choose the best web design company</a> to edit and manage the pages, that web designer to design the pages and a hosting environment. That means major time and money.</p><h3 style="text-align: justify;">Specific requirements for landing pages:</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">The good landing page has many different elements to consider – your landing pages need to be relevant to your keyword and ads in order to earn a good Quality Score. You also need to have conversion tracking properly set up to track what is and is not working.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Follow the steps to improve your landing page experience:</h2><h3 style="text-align: justify;">1. It should be offer relevant, genuine content and Helpful</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Your landing page should contain direct relevant to your google ads text and keywords.</li><li>Provide specific thing while someone clicks on ads. if someone clicks for a particular bike model, they shouldn&#8217;t get all the bikes on the landing page.</li><li>Provide options when a user wants options. if someone’s looking to compare cars, they probably don&#8217;t want to go specific model page. They expect more.</li><li>Give a useful information about whatever you are advertising</li></ul><h3 style="text-align: justify;">2. Increase transparency and loyalty on your website</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Give proper information about your business and what your business does</li><li>Share everything about your product or services before asking visitors to fill out forms</li><li>Show your contact details to find your visitors easily</li><li>Before asking the personal details of the customers, make it clear why you are asking and what you going to do with it</li></ul><h3 style="text-align: justify;">3. Create mobile and computer navigation easy</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Create and design your page well, so people don’t have to hunt around for information.</li><li>Create the best ads that make the peoples order your product.</li><li>when the customers in your landing page don&#8217;t annoy with pop-ups or other features that interfere with their navigation of your site.</li><li>Help the customers to find what they are really expected.</li></ul><h3 style="text-align: justify;">4. Try to Decrease your landing page loading time</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Make it sure your landing page loads quickly once someone clicks on your ad, whether on a computer or mobile device.</li><li>Consider changing your landing page into an Accelerated Mobile Page (AMP).</li><li>Check your site scores on mobile speed, and get quick fixes to improve it.</li></ul><h2 style="text-align: justify;">The Benefits of Using Video on Landing Pages</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">whenever possible you can use the video on your landing pages. It provides a passive engagement medium where visitors can experience your message with very little effort. If you are using video on landing pages can increase conversion by 80%.</p><h3 style="text-align: justify;">Some reasons why video can lift your landing page conversion rates</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Landing page&#8217;s video increase the length of time and people stay on your landing page for more time, giving your brand message longer to sink in.</li><li>If you feature yourself or company employees in the video, the trust factor is raised significantly.</li><li>Customers are lazy and prefer to watch vs. read.</li></ul><p style="text-align: justify;">Nowadays the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/">advantages of digital marketing</a> are huge so the landing pages are very much useful to attract customers who want to buy your product which one you have shown in google ads. The best landing pages increase the sales and collecting customer’s information. Whenever you are going to run Google AdWords try to create a landing page first. We are here in the market to create good looking and attractive landing page.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Here the Best Digital Marketing Company in Bangalore:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">We are CairoCorps Consulting Private Limited, One of India’s Best <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/">digital marketing company in Bangalore</a>. We are offering comprehensive services to your business such as landing page creation, running the digital marketing campaign, web design, mobile application development and <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/">SEO services in Bangalore</a>.<br /> <strong>Contact us for landing page creation and to run the digital marketing campaign&#8230;</strong></p><p><strong>More Tags: </strong><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/">SEO agency in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/interactive-web-solution/">Web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/ecommerce-solutions/">eCommerce website design in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/mobile-application-development/">Mobile application development company in Bangalore</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/">How to use landing pages for your business-2018?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5085</post-id> </item> <item><title>20 Advantages of Digital Marketing over Offline Marketing in 2018 (Infographic)</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 21:11:37 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=4744</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>In current days and the generation where internet and digital media have dominated our lives, so we are unable to do marketing with offline marketing and not feasible for companies to stay away from digital marketing platforms when concerned with promoting their products and services. With the offline and digital marketing discussion going on everywhere, [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/">20 Advantages of Digital Marketing over Offline Marketing in 2018 (Infographic)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;"><img class="wp-image-4745 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/20-Advantages-of-Digital-Marketing-over-Offline-Marketing-in-2018.png?resize=650%2C366&#038;ssl=1" alt="20 Advantages of Digital Marketing over Offline Marketing in 2018" width="650" height="366" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/20-Advantages-of-Digital-Marketing-over-Offline-Marketing-in-2018.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/20-Advantages-of-Digital-Marketing-over-Offline-Marketing-in-2018.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><p style="text-align: justify;">In current days and the generation where internet and digital media have dominated our lives, so we are unable to do marketing with offline marketing and not feasible for companies to stay away from <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>digital marketing</strong></a> platforms when concerned with promoting their products and services. With the offline and digital marketing discussion going on everywhere, let us decide out what is most appropriate for the marketing and development of your business. Online advertising and offline advertising could appear like a hard decision to make but these points will assist you to make up your mind clear.</p><p><span id="more-4744"></span></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Offline marketing is the traditional modes of marketing that have been used since the inception of marketing and advertisements. Offline marketing is treated with advertisements on radio, posters, television, flyers, hoardings, magazines and newspapers.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Digital marketing is the most influential, powerful, important and innovative form of marketing for the growth of your business. It is the greatest method to reach your potential customers. It could be from Google search, social media marketing services, email marketing, and online advertising or pay per click advertising.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Online marketing is more adaptable than offline marketing, though all the types look alike. Now we discuss the benefits of digital marketing and share <strong><u>20</u></strong><u> <strong><em>advantages of digital marketing over offline marketing</em></strong></u> given below:</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><img class="wp-image-4746 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/20-Advantages-of-Digital-Marketing-over-Offline-Marketing-in-2018-Infographic.png?resize=650%2C1625&#038;ssl=1" alt="20 Advantages of Digital Marketing over Offline Marketing in 2018 Infographic" width="650" height="1625" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/20-Advantages-of-Digital-Marketing-over-Offline-Marketing-in-2018-Infographic.png?w=800&amp;ssl=1 800w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/20-Advantages-of-Digital-Marketing-over-Offline-Marketing-in-2018-Infographic.png?resize=120%2C300&amp;ssl=1 120w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/20-Advantages-of-Digital-Marketing-over-Offline-Marketing-in-2018-Infographic.png?resize=768%2C1920&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/20-Advantages-of-Digital-Marketing-over-Offline-Marketing-in-2018-Infographic.png?resize=410%2C1024&amp;ssl=1 410w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/20-Advantages-of-Digital-Marketing-over-Offline-Marketing-in-2018-Infographic.png?resize=600%2C1500&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"></h2><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong style="color: #2f2f2f; font-size: 32px;">Quick and Convenient Marketing:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Digital marketing is quick and convenient marketing when we compared to offline marketing because, at beginning an online marketing campaign, you can actually operate your business anytime a day without having to worry about store hours or overtime payments for digital marketer and staff. Digital marketing is allowing convenient online access to your companies or products or services also is convenient for your possible customers. As more and more customers throughout the world depend on the Internet for everything from purchasing, entertainment to research and education. As a merchant, this is a huge advantage, as it means they can order online right from the support of their home, besides you can easily track sales items online as they make their way into delivery. You can download digital commodities from the internet with simply a click of a mouse also easy to hire a digital marketing company today and many companies providing digital marketing services in Bangalore itself.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong style="color: #2f2f2f; font-size: 32px;">Low Cost for Operations:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Low cost of operations is a crucial advantage of online marketing. The beginning cost of online marketing is only a small amount when it will be compared to newspaper, Yellow Pages, television and radio advertisements cost. For instance, you can receive a local free listing on <a href="https://www.google.com/business/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Google My Business</a> that will be just as powerful as a costly online Yellow Pages advertisement. Besides, while offline advertisement may only run for a small time, a search engine optimization campaign (SEO) can produce long-term results besides you can save lot of money with Pay-Per-Click (PPC) advertising where it is easy to experiment with small advertisement volumes until you perfect your tactics and then increase your online marketing budget and Nowadays you have many PPC company in Bangalore. Huge advertising prices for both visual and print media can be replaced for more effective and minimal costs by following online marketing by building flourishing online marketing.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong style="color: #2f2f2f; font-size: 32px;"><img class="wp-image-4749 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/Digital-Marketing-Advantages.png?resize=650%2C366&#038;ssl=1" alt="Digital Marketing Advantages" width="650" height="366" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/Digital-Marketing-Advantages.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/Digital-Marketing-Advantages.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></strong></h2><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong style="color: #2f2f2f; font-size: 32px;">Targeted Advertising:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">When you are going to market in online, you get the chance to reach your valuable audience based on their class, demographic and geographic. You can decide what kind of people going to focus on the online marketing you want to offer your products or services to customers, besides getting a chance to run targeted marketing campaigns at a large scale is one of the greatest opportunities available to online marketers today. Because the more important to provide an offer or product or services is to a potential customer. The targeted audience is one of the crucial digital marketing advantages.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong style="color: #2f2f2f; font-size: 32px;">Easy to Handle Existing Customer:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">If you know your target customer’s marketing method, you can recognize the optimal time for a particular offer. With following existing customers’ actions, you will be ready to build a purchasing method funnel. In your offer sales first, you need to intimate your existing customer. In this process, digital marketing is very simple through email marketing and bulk SMS you can send huge numbers of emails and SMS to your existing customer within simply mouse click through these things easy to handle your existing customers.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong style="color: #2f2f2f; font-size: 32px;">Easy to Change with Reliable Technology:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">In digital marketing, the digital marketer is following some technologies, changing some technologies and switching technologies. It is impossible to avoid a need to change something in your marketing campaign. But the good news is businesses and online marketing when compared to offline marketing, digital marketing is so much easier to change with reliable technology. The technology that powers the web is reliable. But, better yet, it is becoming better and more sophisticated every day. Delivery of newsletter campaign marketing is instant and, as long as you have the proper address, you don’t have to worry about whether or not it is going to reach its destination.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong style="color: #2f2f2f; font-size: 32px;"><img class="wp-image-4750 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/20-Advantages-of-Digital-Marketing-over-Offline-Marketing3.png?resize=650%2C366&#038;ssl=1" alt="Benefits of Digital Marketing" width="650" height="366" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/20-Advantages-of-Digital-Marketing-over-Offline-Marketing3.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/20-Advantages-of-Digital-Marketing-over-Offline-Marketing3.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></strong></h2><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong style="color: #2f2f2f; font-size: 32px;">Trackable and Measurable Results:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Digital media platforms are being favored by a growing number of companies because the campaigns can be tracked and the results are measurable by the digital marketing advertisers. They obtain insights into how leads are generated and prospects are responding to the campaigns. In addition, they get knowledge on the campaigns that are effective and can also recognize the shortcomings of their businesses. Moreover, they can ascertain if their organizational goals are being met, and if not then they come to realize that then need to reconstruct their future <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/strategy-of-search-engine-optimization/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing and SEO strategies</a> respectively. Is it not great to spend on digital marketing campaign whose results can be measured? Digital marketing allows you to see the measures in real time and presents you a wonderful opportunity to refine the strategy and improve the results</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong style="color: #2f2f2f; font-size: 32px;">Long-term and Immediate Exposure:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Reach many prospects by shifting to a digital marketing operation within a very small investment of your business.  You can get long-term and immediate results by practicing digital marketing. Digital marketing begins up opportunities with an international platform for businesses because even a single digital marketing campaign can be seen worldwide. This is one of the best things in digital marketing and businesses. Costs of starting a campaign against offline marketing methods are considerably very less. However, one should see it as a long-term investment and can also choose Search Engine Optimization (SEO), also you can see huge numbers of SEO agencies Bangalore that provide best SEO services.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong style="color: #2f2f2f; font-size: 32px;">Brand Development and Publicity:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Brand development is what every business strives to achieve and digital marketing accommodates promote your brand by digital marketing services on numerous platforms, the higher viral your brand performs, the higher reputation your brand will get in the eyes of search engines as well as users. Quicker publicity due to the immediate and real-time results of digital marketing, you can receive immediate publicity. If you don’t get quick publicity and brand development, you know at least spontaneously that this particular digital marketing technology is not working for your business so you can switch immediately.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong style="color: #2f2f2f; font-size: 32px;"><img class="wp-image-4751 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/SEO-and-Digital-Marketing.png?resize=650%2C366&#038;ssl=1" alt="SEO and Digital Marketing" width="650" height="366" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/SEO-and-Digital-Marketing.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/SEO-and-Digital-Marketing.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></strong></h2><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong style="color: #2f2f2f; font-size: 32px;">Marketing 24/7:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">In online marketing, you can operate campaigns throughout the clock. It means you are operating digital marketing campaigns anytime (24/7). Compared to offline marketing, digital marketing does not restrain anyone with availability time. Meanwhile, you need not worry about more money pay to your digital marketer or staff. Besides, there is no local or global time variation for you to bother on that will influence the reachability or availability of your digital marketing campaigns. Whenever someone turns on his or her computer or mobile and connects to the internet, there is a higher possibility of them viewing your digital marketing campaigns and customers can see for your product at their most convenient time.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Schedule Future Campaigns:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Digital marketing self-regulation tools make staying regulated easily and properly by allowing you to <a href="https://blog.bufferapp.com/schedule-social-media-content-plan" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">schedule your campaigns and social media posts advanced in time</a>. While this functionality has been throughout since the early days of newsletter campaigns, bulk SMS and social media marketing, the attached benefit of running this from a marketing self-regulation tool are that you can simply schedule various posts to different segments of your customers, based on information in the CRM system you could, for instance, list five small alterations to five different fragments of your customers, all a bit more personalized to their needs and interests.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Greater engagement with Customers:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">By offline marketing, you cannot actually communicate with your target customer. You require waiting out for the customer responses to proceed in before you can organize your further action. This is a lengthy and wearisome process for offline marketer and businesses. Digital marketing permits you to involve your customer in real time and immediate. You can chat, teach and explain a lot about your brand or business with the actual customer instantly. Really, this requires more commitment from your side as well. You want to be prepared to invest that much time into the digital marketing budget.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Non-Intrusive:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Mostly, lots of people avoid getting phone calls and emails in his or her post boxes about the products and services towards which they have the smallest movement. Digital marketing services present astonishing chances to opt out; they are surely less interfering than offline marketing media. You can decide to neglect that email and SMS as long as you want. You can decide to opt out of social media discussions on a particular brand page. You can also target interested customers on the social networking sites grasp a tab on what they look for on the internet.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Data Collection:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">After every digital marketing campaigns and transaction through the internet lets, you collect data easily about your campaigns. It will help your next digital marketing campaigns. Whenever a purchaser purchases something through your website, you get his or her data very clear. You can utilize this data in a lot of ways, but it is most powerful when it is examined to determine what you can do to fine-tune your business. The data collected can also assist to divide the segment of customers so your business can post advertisements and promotional materials based on their interests.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Huge Number of Digital Marketing Companies:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Digital marketing companies in Bangalore and worldwide are expanded to nearly all the sectors. The potential of digital marketing provides geophysical barriers to die to make all customers and companies on the world potential customers and businesses, besides a country with a quickly growing economy; it is expected to have a very high significant growth in the digital marketing career. So you can hire easily a digital marketer and digital marketing company. Here I will suggest, <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>CairoCorps Consulting</em></a> is a best online marketing company in Bangalore also providing content writing services in Bangalore as well.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Connect with Mobile Customers:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Today, most of the people are using the smartphone and using the internet on his or her smartphone so you just cannot neglect the numerous number of smartphone users. All of them should be your target customer if you want to develop your business across the world. It is not the same as sending SMS and making calls. It is fully about using the most outstanding applications that an enormous number of Smartphone users use. You can advertise advertisements to promote your products and services. Besides, your business’s official website should be responsive that means fitted to open all devices. Today all of the website design companies go with the responsive website based on search engine algorithms.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong><img class="wp-image-4752 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/Automated-Digital-Marketing.png?resize=650%2C366&#038;ssl=1" alt="Automated Digital Marketing" width="650" height="366" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/Automated-Digital-Marketing.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/Automated-Digital-Marketing.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></strong></h2><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Automated Marketing:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Just a click, you can run your whole business in digital marketing with an automated tool. When compared with offline marketing, where you must assign various duties to the best sources and talents, digital marketing will apply the latest technology. Also, digital marketing provides you with the chance to transform every appearance of your business’s methods into a fully automated system. All you want to do is determine the right tool and technology appropriate to your digital marketing campaigns whatever you are done. With automating your digital marketing campaign, you can decide to do something more important with your business.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Wider Reachability:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">A company can earn much more publicity on the internet as opposed to broadcasting on television and radio stations that may only be accessible in particular areas and only be viewed by or listened to by a comparatively tiny group of people. One of the advantages of digital marketing over offline marketing is that the former is more far-reaching than the latter. The avenues of digitized technologies are available to any internet or mobile user, unlike the conventional modes which are extremely restricting. For the mobile user, you must develop your website as the <a href="http://responsivedesignchecker.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">responsive mobile website</a>.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Time Effective Marketing:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Compared with offline marketing or traditional marketing, digital marketing is to initiate, run, and implement very easily so it is time and staff effective marketing. The digital marketing tools are run automatically, also have a drag and drop interface, allowing you to build email campaigns, landing pages, and social campaigns with no technical or design expertise required. You can set up email marketing for your business within a short time. Within a couple of minutes, you can set up an autoresponder and generate an email marketing list for your valuable business.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Immediate Transaction:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Doing transaction activities in digital marketing is very easy and almost immediate payment transaction for products and services getting from customers. For this purpose, we have lots of <a href="https://www.dreamhost.com/blog/10-online-payment-gateways-compared/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">online payment gateways</a> for the immediate transaction so it is one of the major benefits of digital marketing.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Focus Globally:</strong></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">One of the highest <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/seo-in-digital-marketing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">benefits of digital marketing within several months of being proactive with SEO</a>, you can have millions of users and reach an enormous customer all around the world. Besides, you have found many SEO experts in Bangalore and worldwide. The world has turned into a global village. All type of business made pleasant through digitization. Digital marketing provides advertisement campaigns to be visible in all part of the world. This provides small start-ups with the occasional opportunity to perform global through the extensive publicity provided. On the internet, you have read many stories of start-ups that became hugely prosperous over a short period due to the opportunities generated gratitude to the global nature of marketing through digital platforms.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">For a small business with fewer budgets to spend on marketing activities can use digital marketing to target the narrow group of customers and focus heavily on them. Digital marketing offers a wide range of options to market your business to potential customers. Nowadays all business must have digital visibility and cannot be left behind as it affects the online and offline customers.</p><h3><strong>Obtain the Best Digital Marketing Package from CairoCorps Consulting:</strong></h3><p style="text-align: justify;">CairoCorps Consulting is a complete web development &amp; design, SEO and <strong><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing agency in Bangalore</a></strong>, India. We provide creative digital solutions to bring your products and services to a wider public. With our branding and user-centered design, customers are engaged and brand awareness grows. Our impressive client list trusts us to deliver creative, interactive experiences for their customers across the whole range of web and mobile applications.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/">20 Advantages of Digital Marketing over Offline Marketing in 2018 (Infographic)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">4744</post-id> </item> </channel> </rss>