<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
><channel><title>website development company in Bangalore &#8211; CairoCorps Consulting</title> <atom:link href="https://cairocorps.com/tag/website-development-company-in-bangalore/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><link>https://cairocorps.com</link> <description>Creations &#124; Digital Transformations</description> <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 10:31:14 +0000</lastBuildDate> <language>en-US</language> <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod> <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency><image> <url>https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/ccc-logo-1.png?fit=25%2C32&#038;ssl=1</url><title>website development company in Bangalore &#8211; CairoCorps Consulting</title><link>https://cairocorps.com</link> <width>32</width> <height>32</height> </image> <site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">142080933</site> <item><title>Content Management System Used by Web Design Company</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/content-management-system-used-by-web-design-company/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/content-management-system-used-by-web-design-company/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 11:23:26 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web designers in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web development company Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5288</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Content Management System Used by Web Design Company Welcome to the Modern world with amazing technologies. Most of the time peoples busy using technologies. Everyone expecting everything in their hand. Even technology gave that too. nowadays everyone having some kind of gadgets in their pockets. It&#8217;s entirely changed their life. They look at the online [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/content-management-system-used-by-web-design-company/">Content Management System Used by Web Design Company</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure id="attachment_5290" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="size-large wp-image-5290" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-Used-by-Web-Design-Company-1024x512.jpg?resize=1024%2C512&#038;ssl=1" alt="Content Management System Used by Web Design Company" width="1024" height="512" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-Used-by-Web-Design-Company.jpg?w=1024&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-Used-by-Web-Design-Company.jpg?resize=300%2C150&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-Used-by-Web-Design-Company.jpg?resize=768%2C384&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-Used-by-Web-Design-Company.jpg?resize=700%2C350&amp;ssl=1 700w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-Used-by-Web-Design-Company.jpg?resize=600%2C300&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Content Management System Used by Web Design Company</figcaption></figure><h1>Content Management System Used by Web Design Company</h1><p>Welcome to the Modern world with amazing technologies. Most of the time peoples busy using technologies. Everyone expecting everything in their hand. Even technology gave that too. nowadays everyone having some kind of gadgets in their pockets. It&#8217;s entirely changed their life. They look at the online and get to know which services, products are the best in the market. If someone has a website for his or her business is giving more return to them for making more business and more money. Attracting and powerful websites giving more traffic to your websites. More traffic more business. Hope you much heard about content management system. For creating attracting website choose the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com">best web designing company</a>. CairoCorps is One of the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com">best website developers in Bangalore</a></p><p>Create and maintaining a website is an overwhelming task for every business when we don’t have much knowledge in the content management system and don’t have a web development team. But the most defective thing is outdated information’s can cost a company in many ways. The good solution we need to maintain the website will depend on good CMS.</p><p>All the websites come with a content management system. It means we have full access to modify the content, images and all at day and night. Just log in to the website and do the changes on our own. All the websites come with an ample amount of training so don’t worry about it. Mostly we are using WordPress, Joomla, Magento or Drupal. These are all the most effective Content Management Systems in the current periods.</p><p>&nbsp;</p><h2>Content Management System (CMS)</h2><p>&nbsp;</p><p>CMS is a web application that makes us modify the content and images easily. No need of any technical knowledge for access this. The user can easily build websites, streamline the web publishing procedure and deployed easily. We can create content-rich websites. Many open source CMS look easier but technically its need more development effort, they work on it and deploy it and customize the website. Then only they will create a suitable CMS for your requirements.</p><p>Cairocorps CMS developers have vast expertise in a lot of CMS platforms. So they will give a good solution for all your requirements. they build amazing websites and CMS. If you need any content management system requirements to ask India’s Largest <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com">web development company in Bangalore</a>. Learn more about web development <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com">click here</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Cairocorps have large of experience to develop websites and web applications, they also use most of the Open Source  Content Management Systems like Joomla!, WordPress, Mambo, Drupal, osCommerce, DotNetNuke and Pligg CMS. Pick your suitable one for your business</p><h3>Brief about Content Management Systems</h3><p>The website design is no longer limited to static HTML pages. Nowadays businesses have to deal with daily basis so the information’s are increasing daily. Updating a static site is taking more time, we need to enter the coding part and change the contents if we do this definitely we need to know some technical knowledge. Its take much time and a lot of manpower required. This what we are using a content management system.it gives the solution without wasting any time and not needed any technical knowledge as well.</p> <figure id="attachment_5291" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com"><img class="wp-image-5291 size-large" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-1024x732.jpg?resize=1024%2C732&#038;ssl=1" alt="best website developers in Bangalore" width="1024" height="732" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System.jpg?resize=1024%2C732&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System.jpg?resize=300%2C214&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System.jpg?resize=768%2C549&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System.jpg?resize=1140%2C814&amp;ssl=1 1140w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System.jpg?resize=600%2C429&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">best website developers in Bangalore</figcaption></figure><p>A content management system (<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Content_management_system">CMS</a>) handles all your dynamic content and website needs from an easy to use backend solution. CMS developed websites are easy to maintain, update with better and simple control panel. Which ultimately amplified your productivity and most importantly you don&#8217;t have to be technically professional to do required changes.</p><p>CMS handles all the dynamic contents and websites needs from back-end solution. CMS makes the websites are easy to use and maintain, updates with better and simple control panel. It obviously increases productivity and definitely, you don’t need any technical knowledge to change the website contents. We can update daily basis.</p><p>If your business running by using a simple static website don’t worry switch your website as a dynamic one. Are you looking for a technical person support daily for changing the content means it is a huge burden? Take a good step to move into a Dynamic website with cairocorps. Dynamic websites have come with a lot of highly functional, responsive web design and Content Management System too.</p><p>Know something about <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites/">Static and Dynamic website differents</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><h3>Companies provide the following CMS design and development services.</h3><ul><li>Web content management services</li><li>Component content management systems</li><li>Enterprise content management systems</li><li>Corporate CMS</li><li>Joomla Development</li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WordPress">WordPress</a> Design and Integration</li><li>Magneto ecommerce CMS</li></ul><h3></h3><h3>Why companies are giving more preference to CMS than other website development services?</h3><p>Some of the given features make the companies choose CMS. It gives more features. Have a look below</p><ul><li>SEO friendly website – Search engine perform in a friendly way good for user and search engines, If our websites are supported SEO we can do some Search engine Optimizing works and come first in the search engines. Its automatically give more business and growth.</li><li>Multiple languages – If we run the business all over the world we should keep the website in multiple languages. Then only our customers join with us easily. So we should provide the languages by their location, Its possible in Dynamic websites.</li><li>Social Media Integrations – We can make our website as social friendly which gives more useful things. We can fully leverage of leading social platform like facebook, twitter and lot more. If we are more active in social media it also gives more business. Ask how</li><li>Customization &#8211; Customization is one of the best features comes with CMS developed websites. We don’t worry about the updates coming in future.</li></ul><p>Cairocorps is one of the leading <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com">web design company in Bangalore</a>. we create full fledge CMS enabled websites and we give proper training to update the content and images by your own. We give an effective content management system with full features. Please contact us to know more about our open source Content Management Systems.</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/content-management-system-used-by-web-design-company/">Content Management System Used by Web Design Company</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/content-management-system-used-by-web-design-company/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5288</post-id> </item> <item><title>Importance of Web Design</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/importance-of-web-design/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/importance-of-web-design/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 06:22:23 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web development company Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5265</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Importance of Web Design The current day a lot of businessmen is spending huge money on their web design process and digital marketing. Behind this have many reasons I found some businessmen they are running their business through the website only that is why they are spending huge money on website design process besides they [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/importance-of-web-design/">Importance of Web Design</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="size-large wp-image-5266 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Importance-of-Web-Design-1024x512.png?resize=1024%2C512&#038;ssl=1" alt="Importance of Web Design, website design company" width="1024" height="512" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Importance-of-Web-Design.png?w=1024&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Importance-of-Web-Design.png?resize=300%2C150&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Importance-of-Web-Design.png?resize=768%2C384&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Importance-of-Web-Design.png?resize=700%2C350&amp;ssl=1 700w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Importance-of-Web-Design.png?resize=600%2C300&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1><span style="font-size: xx-large;"><b>Importance of Web Design</b></span></h1><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The current day a lot of businessmen is spending huge money on their web design process and digital marketing. Behind this have many reasons I found some businessmen they are running their business through the website only that is why they are spending huge money on website design process besides they are spending huge money on digital marketing includes SEO, PPC, Bulk SMS, newsletter campaigns and etc&#8230; In this article, I am going to discuss the importance of web design for business, blogger, NGOs, and anything.<br /> While we come to highlight your online presence, If you run a business or sell a service or product, it is highly paramount that the quality and prices of respective products or services. Importance of web design is based on the penetration of smartphone, computer, internet, and electronic devices there are many things that you want to put into great consideration. Anything does this really indicate to online marketers? Fundamentally, the act of building your online presence in the market does not simply finish by just designing a basic website for your business or company. besides, you must adopt some digital marketing strategy includes SEO, PPC, SMM, Bulk SMS, and newsletter campaign to boost your business. We are considering the only website is the main tool of digital marketing that is without website we cant move further that is all.<br /> We can see today a lot of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Startup_company" target="_blank" rel="noopener">startups</a> striving to build their foot in the market. Nevertheless, it is a painful fact that several of them lose to reach as much targeted audience as they expect in the first place. Which brings them for losing? It is mainly because they undervalue the capability of a created website to earn business for them. Website development for startups plans can demonstrate very fruitful. You must consider your website should be an asset. Let us look at some of the important reasons why a website is important for business growth.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: large;"><b>Some of The Importance of Web Design</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">As a businessman, you must to know where are your customers. There are various factors that lead to a successful online presence in the market. But before going on any further, let’s know first How exactly important web design is it?</span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: medium;"><b><span style="font-size: large;">24/7 Accessibility</span></b></span></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">When we arrive up with a startup or business plan and initially Everyone establishes a physical office or store for your company, through that you might get audience throughout the daytime or when you are there. People are quite busy with their daily life So, Visiting Your office is not possible for everyone. If you hold a website for your business strategy as an online forum, there is a huge chance of getting a lot of audiences online to link up with you. This has happened because people are piped up with internet in day and night. People prefer to get into everything the easy way with good quality is possible. Your website has some content with all the basic information and data. They will be able to access website 24/7.</span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-family: brandon-grotesque, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: large;">Increase in Mobile Usage</span></span></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-family: brandon-grotesque, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: medium;">All studies are come out regards mobile usages of today reflected huge increasing trends. It is proving a real surge in mobile usage. The usability of 4G has also influenced how people use their mobile devices. then, it was reported that two-thirds of people had a smartphone, with most of the internet users admitting their smartphone was the most important device for going online. All are spent twice as long online on our smartphones than laptops or personal computers. Many studies are demonstrating </span><span style="font-family: brandon-grotesque, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: medium;">just how many people browse on their smartphones and tablets instead of a laptop or desktop computer. This highlighted an exciting turn in smartphone users so through a <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web design company</a> to get a responsive website immediately.</span></span></span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><strong><span style="font-family: brandon-grotesque, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: large;">Penetration of Internet</span></span></strong></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-family: brandon-grotesque, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Above half of the world’s people is now online, with the latest study revealing that almost a quarter of a billion new internet users came online for the first time in 2017. While comparing in India&#8217;s metropolitan cities around 80% of people using internet some of the studies are showing this results so this is a good time to go online otherwise never survive in your business to choose the best <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/">digital marketing company</a> for your business.</span></span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-family: walkway ultraboldregular, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: large;">Search Engine Optimization</span></span></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-family: brandon-grotesque, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Over 650 million websites and another 51 million added each year, there is huge online competition for your services or products. We looked at several ways to make your website stand out aesthetically, but there are also ways to help it stand out on search engines. Search engine visibility is very important to your website because most of the businessmen are getting leads through google&#8217;s visibility. Being on the first page of search engine search for your services is crucial to your online conversions. <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Search_engine_optimization">Search Engine Optimization</a> (SEO) is which assist your website rank well with search engines. Hire is an <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/seo-company-in-bangalore/">SEO company</a> that can be performed SEO services on your website. An important factor you should consider when developing a website it should SEO friendly websites.</span></span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: large;"><b>Looking for Web Design Company in Bangalore?</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">These are some of the importance of web design for your business. Web design is not just designing a good looking website, it should be user-friendly. a website is an asset of your business If you are not having a website <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/">contact us </a>for prices. you have any suggestion regarding this post let us know&#8230;</span></p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/importance-of-web-design/">Importance of Web Design</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/importance-of-web-design/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5265</post-id> </item> <item><title>YouTube Outage In 2018</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 07:22:24 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[seo company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web development company in banglore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5252</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>YouTube Outage In 2018 YouTube is top social media for videos in worldwide it&#8217;s running successfully with lakhs of subscriber and channel. In these YouTube, YouTube TV, and YouTube music down around one hour then it&#8217;s back on Wednesday (16/10/2018). As per web development company in Bangalore, we discuss what happened YouTube around one hour [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/">YouTube Outage In 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="size-full wp-image-5253 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/youtube-outage-2018.jpg?resize=759%2C422&#038;ssl=1" alt="YouTube outage 2018, web design company in Bangalore" width="759" height="422" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/youtube-outage-2018.jpg?w=759&amp;ssl=1 759w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/youtube-outage-2018.jpg?resize=300%2C167&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/youtube-outage-2018.jpg?resize=600%2C334&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 759px) 100vw, 759px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1>YouTube Outage In 2018</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">YouTube is top social media for videos in worldwide it&#8217;s running successfully with lakhs of subscriber and channel. In these YouTube, YouTube TV, and YouTube music down around one hour then it&#8217;s back on Wednesday (16/10/2018). As per <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web development company in Bangalore</a>, we discuss what happened YouTube around one hour and how it was rectified.</p><h2>what happened YouTube</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">A lot of users has reported regards getting &#8220;500 internal server error&#8221; on him/her display. In this global outrage was happened across the world and user was reported continuously from across the world because unable to access or upload content on YouTube. YouTube was felt a major outage in that history. Users across the world began to notice that the video service’s sites and mobile application were down around 9:20 PM ET, and everything continues inaccessible more than an hour later. YouTube TV and YouTube Music are also affected by the service interruption.</p><p><img class="size-full wp-image-5254 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_2.png?resize=761%2C406&#038;ssl=1" alt="YouTube outrage 2018, web development company in bangalore" width="761" height="406" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_2.png?w=761&amp;ssl=1 761w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_2.png?resize=300%2C160&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_2.png?resize=600%2C320&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 761px) 100vw, 761px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2>YouTube team had rectified the issue:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">After getting a lot of reports from users, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCC32iZBJCrDJONbYRlLiW0A" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a> has confirmed the global outage in a tweet. “We’re working on resolving this and will let you know once fixed,” besides the Team YouTube account says. “We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause and will keep you updated.” Since of 10.35PM ET, the account is still responding to reports of the global outage saying that the team is working on the problem.</p><p><img class="size-full wp-image-5255 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_3.png?resize=676%2C270&#038;ssl=1" alt="YouTube issue in 2018, best web design company in bangalore" width="676" height="270" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_3.png?w=676&amp;ssl=1 676w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_3.png?resize=300%2C120&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_3.png?resize=600%2C240&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 676px) 100vw, 676px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><p style="text-align: justify;">YouTube&#8217;s technical team was working to find the issue of down on YouTube. Finally, the team was found an issue that is the server and YouTube team has rectified the server issue. YouTube&#8217;s global outage was lasting around one hour. Finally, YouTube asked sorry to all users through <a href="https://twitter.com/CairoCorps" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a>. Now YouTube is running successfully all over the world.</p><p><img class="size-full wp-image-5256 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?resize=793%2C357&#038;ssl=1" alt="YouTube problem, website development company in bangalore" width="793" height="357" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?w=793&amp;ssl=1 793w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?resize=300%2C135&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?resize=768%2C346&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?resize=600%2C270&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 793px) 100vw, 793px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/">YouTube Outage In 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5252</post-id> </item> <item><title>Best Places to Put Contact Forms in Website</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 08:14:39 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web development company in banglore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5203</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Best Places to Put Contact Forms in Website The Contact Forms or Enquiry Forms are called Lead Generation Forms in Business Terms. Because these forms get the details of the user based on the interest the user has in your website or Business Landing Page. The UI/UX makes the user trust the website and makes [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website/">Best Places to Put Contact Forms in Website</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="size-large wp-image-5204 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website-1024x512.png?resize=1024%2C512&#038;ssl=1" alt="best places to put contact forms in website, web design company in Bangalore, web development company in Bangalore" width="1024" height="512" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website.png?w=1024&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website.png?resize=300%2C150&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website.png?resize=768%2C384&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website.png?resize=700%2C350&amp;ssl=1 700w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website.png?resize=600%2C300&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1>Best Places to Put Contact Forms in Website</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">The Contact Forms or Enquiry Forms are called Lead Generation Forms in Business Terms. Because these forms get the details of the user based on the interest the user has in your website or Business <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Landing_page" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Landing Page</a>. The UI/UX makes the user trust the website and makes him/her provide the details those we required to use in our business.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">You need to make sure that You are making it very easy for the user to provide the details by placing contact forms an inappropriate place of the website in order to get more inquiries from the visitors.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">In this article, we will show you up the best places to place the forms on your Website or Landing page</p><h2>Get More Leads from Contact Forms</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">All Websites are evolving through the best practices to put more details about the business to visitors to get the good understanding of it. No matter which industry you belongs to:</p><ul><li>A Business owner needs of customers</li><li>A sales guy require Leads</li><li>An <a href="https://ecommerceguide.com/guides/what-is-ecommerce/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">eCommerce</a> Store looking for maximum sales conversion</li><li>An R&amp;D Team looking for client feedbacks.</li></ul><p style="text-align: justify;">The Website should be able to guide the user to scan through the page to get the idea to help the visitor understand what is about and what you’re looking from them.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">A <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">best web design company</a> practices the A/B testing for the better placement of forms and Contents with a Good Website designer.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">You need to place a call to action buttons or pop-up forms or some sort of things to make your client guide through to fill the forms. The form can be anything as your business needs like newsletter form or inquiry form or even a SignUp Form.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">So, How will you decide what is the best place and practice put the right form in right place? Well, Read on…</p><h2>Here are some good place and practices to place many types of forms:</h2><h3>i) Side Bars</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">One of the easily readable positions of any web page is a sidebar. You can place any form over there with other contents or Menu Links to seek the visitors’ attention. How To articles or Blog posts have a high conversion rate for Sidebars but it’s not only limited to these.</p><p>A Typical Sidebar form looks like below:</p><p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-5205" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/ninja-kick-sidebar-contact-form.jpg?resize=313%2C550&#038;ssl=1" alt="contact forms, web design company in bangalore, web development company in Bangalore" width="313" height="550" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/ninja-kick-sidebar-contact-form.jpg?w=313&amp;ssl=1 313w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/ninja-kick-sidebar-contact-form.jpg?resize=171%2C300&amp;ssl=1 171w" sizes="(max-width: 313px) 100vw, 313px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><p style="text-align: justify;">You can get an advice from a <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web development company in Bangalore</a> for this website enhancement. We focus worldwide from Bangalore.</p><h3>ii) Contact Page</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">The name stands for itself, The Contact Page generally have contact information. By Placing Forms over there, We have a better probability to get the visitor filling the form as the Business contact details also provided explicitly.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">But make sure that you are explaining clearly why the visitors have to give their details in the form. List your contact details including phone number, Address, and Emails.</p><p><img class="size-large wp-image-5206 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website-1024x589.png?resize=1024%2C589&#038;ssl=1" alt="Best Places to put Contact Forms in Website, web development company in Bangalore, web design company in Bangalore" width="1024" height="589" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website.png?resize=1024%2C589&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website.png?resize=300%2C173&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website.png?resize=768%2C442&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website.png?resize=1140%2C656&amp;ssl=1 1140w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website.png?resize=600%2C345&amp;ssl=1 600w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website.png?w=1200&amp;ssl=1 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h3>iii) About Page</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">As you will be detailing about the Organization or Business &#8211; You are already gaining the trust of the visitor. Thus placing the Form here will also yield the results and attention of the visitor. You can place minimal forms such as contact or Newsletter here in the page in midst of the contents or in the sidebar or underneath of the page.</p><h3>iv) Footer</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Always try to place a newsletter form in the footer which is clearly visible to the visitor in all the pages. Forms with very minimal fields can go in the footer. Usually, the users will look for more link about the business in the footer, So if they could get periodic details about your business in the format of a newsletter, They are ready to invest the space for a form.</p><h3>v) Sliding bars and Pop-Ups</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">The attention-seeking pop-ups or actionable items are always a good place to put a Form by making the visitor to enjoy more benefits like offers or secrets or tips. The visitors will be eager to receive these by filling a form if your actionable item is eye catch or having better Look and feel.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">All these methods will surely help you to maximize lead generation. Please comment your thoughts and more findings. We will update our article if required. Thanks!</p><p style="text-align: justify;">If you need any help on any Web User Experience, Contact Us today. CairoCorps is committed to providing the best service to satisfy clients. It’s one of the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">best web design company in Bangalore</a>.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">And don’t forget, if you like this article, then please follow us on Facebook and Twitter.</p><p><strong>More Tags: </strong><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website design company in Bangalore</a></p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website/">Best Places to Put Contact Forms in Website</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5203</post-id> </item> <item><title>Benefits of Responsive Web Design-2018</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 11:42:27 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web designers in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web development company Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website design companies in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website designers in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website development company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[list of web development companies in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[responsive web design bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[responsive web design company bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[responsive web design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[top web design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design services in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web development services bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website designers in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website developers in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5162</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Benefits of Responsive Web Design-2018 We are lived among the peoples either they are educated or illiterate. In this modern world every one looking for the change even if they don&#8217;t know about the technology. Previous days if anyone getting any doubts they may get to know either from someone or from books. But nowadays [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-2018/">Benefits of Responsive Web Design-2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class=" wp-image-5163 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-1.png?resize=649%2C365&#038;ssl=1" alt="benefits of responsive web design, web design company in bangalore" width="649" height="365" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-1.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-1.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 649px) 100vw, 649px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1>Benefits of Responsive Web Design-2018</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">We are lived among the peoples either they are educated or illiterate. In this modern world every one looking for the change even if they don&#8217;t know about the technology. Previous days if anyone getting any doubts they may get to know either from someone or from books. But nowadays they have an easy way to know everything by the using of Google. Now everyone using google for getting knowledge, images, videos and etc. Now it&#8217;s become a part of life.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Many businesses running by using the internet and that makes them as multi-millionaire like Amazon, Flipkart, and more e-commerce businesses. Moreover, most of the businesses only depending on the internet. So as a business person we should show our presence in front of the world. How can we do that? I&#8217;ll give you the solution, try to <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">choose the best web design company</a> who give the best website for affordable price. After that, you just portray who you are and what you are going to selling. The world looking for an easy way that makes them more comfortable without any hurdles.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Website design companies having more types of websites like static, dynamic, e-Commerce and etc. You just Portray who you just pick static one. If you going to do regular updates ill suggest you take dynamic one. You have more products that you are going to sell in online means don’t hesitate to take the e-Commerce website. Are you a writer just pick the blogging website. Similarly, we have a lot of choices before choosing yours try to consult with a good <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website development company</a>. They will give proper guidance about it.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Most important things on your website to be compatible with all devices, In olden days websites, are not useful for anything now it’s a business market for enlarging your business. So I would suggest doing its responsive. why I&#8217;m saying like that and what is the use of that? Below I&#8217;ll say you all the benefits and its making process.</p><p><img class="wp-image-5164 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/benefits-of-responsive-web-design.png?resize=670%2C377&#038;ssl=1" alt="advantages of responsive web design, web design company in bangalore" width="670" height="377" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/benefits-of-responsive-web-design.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/benefits-of-responsive-web-design.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 670px) 100vw, 670px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: left;">History of Responsive Website Design</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Before proceeding how it will make I would like to say its history, The first website designed to adapt its layout based on the width of the browser is Audi.com. They are the one who created the device-adaptive website. It was launched in 2001. After 2011 the developer Ethan Marcotte use the same type of technology and phase it <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Responsive_web_design" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Responsive Web Design</a>, Marcotte wrote a book on the subject in 2011 simply titled “Responsive Web Design.”</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">8-Important Benefits of Responsive Web Design</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Nowadays everyone has a mobile in their hand, They were getting everything from there. So as a business people we should satisfy our customers by providing good looking and compatible websites for all device, Its more useful to convert them as our customer. The first approach is more important than anything. So Responsive websites are more important for recent days.</p><p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-5165 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/eda.jpg?resize=560%2C315&#038;ssl=1" alt="" width="560" height="315" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/eda.jpg?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/eda.jpg?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 560px) 100vw, 560px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h3>1. Mobile Users Increased</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">By the statics, the mobile users are increased after 2014. So they mobile traffic is increased. Most of the peoples are searching in mobile, Therefore the companies to have websites and that should adaptable for all devices. If you created a website in the responsive way its suitable for Mobile, Tablets and all types of screens. While some companies are creating the separate version for their mobile view customers.</p><h3>2. Faster and low cost</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Create one Responsive website considerable less time and low cost than making a stand-alone mobile application and a standard desktop website. Initial develop cost only the investment of developing a responsive website. No more maintenance cost and special configuration cost.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">3. Maintenance Cost is low</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Maintaining a separate mobile site need to test and support. In contrast, the responsive use standardizing testing methods to ensure optimal layout on every screen. If we have two type of desktop and mobile sites mean, we concentrate on two type of content strategies and two administrative interfaces and two different designing teams. Responsive designs take less time and low cost for maintaining the site.</p><h3>4.Fast Loading Web pages</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Mobile users are having short-term attention spans. Studies say that the mobile users tend to abandon web pages that take longer than three seconds to finish loading. So as a provider we should give easy and fast loading web pages. When we going to responsive design it gives faster loading for mobiles and other devices. Its using modern performance techniques such as caching and image display will help to improve your web pages loading speed.</p><p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-5166 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/advantages-of-responsive-web-design.png?resize=900%2C300&#038;ssl=1" alt="benefits of responsive web design, web design company in bangalore" width="900" height="300" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/advantages-of-responsive-web-design.png?w=900&amp;ssl=1 900w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/advantages-of-responsive-web-design.png?resize=300%2C100&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/advantages-of-responsive-web-design.png?resize=768%2C256&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/advantages-of-responsive-web-design.png?resize=600%2C200&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h3>5. Reduce Bouncing Rate</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">If you know about Search Engine Optimization definitely have an idea about the bouncing rate. A responsive and optimized mobile site gives a much better user experience for the customers. Therefore, if the customer like our page they will stick around for a long period of time and explore more pages of our site. Alternatively, if our site isn’t responsive it is much harder to keep the customers on our website and at the end, the bouncing rate will increase.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">6. Conversion Rate will Increase</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Creating consisting user experience across all device is key to converting new customers. Having a single secure website that looks professional on all platforms make the user less likely to get frustrated or turn to a competitor.</p><h3>7. Getting Easy Analytics</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">You can easily find out the way how the users come and where they go to your site. It helps us to improve our website and its pages. In responsive design, we will give the good experience to the customers and they are spending much time in our site. We have a single site so it&#8217;s not much harder to analyze your site. <a href="https://analytics.google.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Google Analytics</a> and similar tools now cater to the responsive website by condense tracking and analytics into a single report so that you can find how your contents are performing on different devices.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">8.Successful in SEO</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">In responsive websites every content is optimized clearly, it will give full satisfaction to the visitor, So the bouncing rate is improving day by day, it gives good google ranking. The contents are updated in a single admin and it will reflect all devices. Stronger backlinks and better bounce rates translate into higher search rankings, but there’s an extra SEO benefit for mobile-optimized sites. This is crucial because of SEO one digital marketing strategy. <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Advantages of digital marketing</a> are huge.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Those are the advantages of a responsive web design. This is essential for any kind of website. Responsive web design provides the best experience for your website visitors. If you desire to be on top you have to make a responsive website for your business. As you can get it is beneficial for you to have a responsive web design presently and for the future.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Bespoke Responsive Web Design Company in Bangalore</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">CairoCorps is one of the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/">best web design companies in Bangalore</a> besides we provide comprehensive digital marketing services such as SEO, PPC, SMM, SMO, etc&#8230; If you have any inquiries about responsive web design please let us know. You&#8217;re needed your website redesigned responsively contact us now!</p><p><strong>More Tags: </strong><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEO agency in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/interactive-web-solution/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/ecommerce-solutions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">e-commerce developers Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/mobile-application-development/">mobile application development company in Bangalore</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-2018/">Benefits of Responsive Web Design-2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5162</post-id> </item> <item><title>10 steps website design processes for startup -2018</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 08:14:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web development company Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website design companies in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[top web design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design services in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5149</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>10 Steps Website Design Processes for Startup-2018 The website is crucial for every business because marketing in business is an essential thing while doing marketing every one should move according to the latest and influenced marketing. Nowadays every one knew digital marketing better than traditional marketing because of internet penetration across global besides having lots [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018/">10 steps website design processes for startup -2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="wp-image-5150 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/10-steps-website-design-processes-for-startup-2018.png?resize=601%2C338&#038;ssl=1" alt="10 steps website design processes for startup -2018, web design company in bangalore" width="601" height="338" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/10-steps-website-design-processes-for-startup-2018.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/10-steps-website-design-processes-for-startup-2018.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 601px) 100vw, 601px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1><strong><span style="font-size: x-large;">10 Steps Website Design Processes for Startup-2018</span></strong></h1><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The website is crucial for every business because marketing in business is an essential thing while doing marketing every one should move according to the latest and influenced marketing. Nowadays every one knew digital marketing better than traditional marketing because of internet penetration across global besides having lots of <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/">advantages of digital marketing</a>. The website is one of the biggest tools of the digital marketing process. web design is a little tough task. You are constantly developing your design until you reach the viewpoint. The web design’s progress depends on how well you connect elements such as lines, fonts, colors, images, design, and textures to describe a company’s mission and vision. The attention is extremely essential during each part of the process of website design. You want to get into website design for your startup literally you have many doubts Where do I start? How do I start? How can I <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/">choose the best web design company</a>? Here I explain the details of the 10 steps website design process for startups-2018.</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Your startup needs a website which includes professional and eye-catchy and this can be a tricky perspective for your website design to complete. Luckily there are 10 steps website design process you can follow on which can assist the website design process move easily. You have taken the strong step to commence your own startups business, fine now let&#8217;s take a little effort to design the website for your startups.</span></p><p style="text-align: center;"><img class="alignnone wp-image-5151" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/website-design-processes-for-startup.png?resize=602%2C338&#038;ssl=1" alt="website design processes for startup -2018, website development company in bangalore" width="602" height="338" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/website-design-processes-for-startup.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/website-design-processes-for-startup.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Keep Design Simple</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The most common suggestion from my client&#8217;s side about their website design is &#8216;makes it simple and unique&#8217;. The website shows the brand name of your startup so it must impress the guests. A simple website without unnecessary distractions is less overwhelming, particularly for first-time guests. By a less intricate design, users will be able to keep their focus on the content they are looking for. Presently be sure to make the information on your site clear and short to engage their attention; because a really effective website design doesn’t just look great, it also helps the content efficiently so make simple your websites.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Content Creation</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Content is always the king of your website can seldom be the stimulating part of your website. It requires to attract the visitors and convey the right kind of information at the top level so guests actually read it instead of jumping on to the other website. When you write content, imagine twice about it from an advertising viewpoint. Besides to content, you also need to add attractive images and graphics are commonly used to increase the text content or seldom even replace it. Earning the pages professional viewing is especially significant as visual influence and attraction is a key part of any website. The website is an area where you should use content, images, videos, graphics, infographics and unless you are very good at generating these things, you might need to hunt a <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/">web design company</a> to assist you.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Page Load Time</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">When you design a website page loading speed is crucial because guests have no patience for your websites with lower load speeds performance.A study said, touching half of the web users anticipate the website to load in 2 seconds or less. If it isn’t loaded within 3 seconds, users lead to abandoning the respective website. That indicates you’re not only losing your current guests and reducing conversion rates, though you run the risk of your website losing traffic from those customers who may have referred your website to others. With that in mind, let’s try to get the speedy website for your startup and optimize your website for the best potential performance.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Make User-Friendly</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">User-friendly website developing is the art of making your website and easy to use. Knowing your customer’s online presence provides you insight into what does and what doesn&#8217;t. The mystery lies in proper preparation and thorough experiment behind the user-friendly website. Largest established companies have a step in their project progress especially the website designed to identify and eliminate possible user-friendly issues. It typically has no website design elements or color; preferably it concentrates on something. The sole focus is on content, structure, flow, and functionality without other visuals to distract the eye. so try to design the user-friendly website for your startup.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Clear Call to Action</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The purpose of designing an e-commerce website or any website is to obtain it helpful for users to buy products and services or other purposes. A simplistic approach of encouraging progress is by including Clear Call to Action(CTA) in the website such as buttons, images, and links followed by an actionable text that demonstrates to the guests the outcome of their actions. If your website has been receiving a lot of traffic, but the conversion rate does not resemble to be good enough, among the many possible reasons, there often is the absence of well-designed and strategically located CTAs. Placing of CTAs is very important for your website so the consultation of the website designer keep it proper.</span></p><p><img class=" wp-image-5152 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018.png?resize=570%2C321&#038;ssl=1" alt="website design processes for startup -2018, website design services in bangalore" width="570" height="321" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 570px) 100vw, 570px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Case Studies</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Case studies are a marketing hook of your startup. Companies use them to show how their product or service has been completed successfully and delivered to customers. Rather than just talking about a product or services, case studies empower businesses to show how their product or services can be used. An efficient case study will incorporate similar elements of your startup while designing website placed correct place or arrange separate page for the case study in your website.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Links to Social Pages</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Social media profiles work properly with your startup website to improve your online business of startup. Applying links on your website plays a vital role in its search engine rankings. Google will automatically connect your social media pages with your company when recognizing the links on your website. There is the huge number of ways to combine your social media presence on your startup website. Have many advantages to attaching social media such as <a href="https://www.facebook.com/CairoCorps/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://plus.google.com/+CairoCorpsConsulting">Google+</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/cairocorps/" class="broken_link">LinkedIn</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/cairocorps/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://in.pinterest.com/cairocorps/">Pinterest</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/CairoCorps">Twitter</a> and etc to your website. The help of a website builder to add social media pages to your website its an easy process.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Make the Website Responsive</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Today most of the people spend the time on browsing your favorite websites or social media or ordering things through the mobile phone. Most of the people owned the smartphone, it is important that your website looks good and works well on all devices. That is why all websites must fit responsive web design. Responsive web design is the practice of building a website suitable to run on every device and every screen size, no matter how large or small, mobile or desktop. Responsive web design is concentrated around providing an intuitive and satisfying user experience for everyone regardless of the device they use to access your website so must design the responsive website for your startup.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Add Some Fun</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The main goal of all projects that we need them to make an impression on people. We want the websites that we create to be remarkable. A fun activity is usually an enjoyable one and an enjoyable experience is usually an interesting thing. Hence, it attains to mind that one of the ways to create a memorable experience is to make it a fun experience. we take a look at how adding a little fun into the mix can help us produce more engaging and expectedly more successful so add some fun to your website.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>SEO Friendly</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Most of the people know how much important of Search Engine Optimization(SEO) when comes on online presence. Although there is no getting ranking without satisfying the Google bot. This means is developing an SEO plan that satisfies the requirements of your brand and consumers. the step is creating an SEO compliance website. If the website you have isn’t optimized, then it’ll fight to get to the top of the search engine page results. Hold in your mind that users seldom go beyond the first page of search engines. So get it as SEO friendly websites.</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong><span style="font-size: medium;">Do you have the suggestion other hints and best exercises for website design processes for startup-2018? Comment here&#8230;</span></strong></p><p><strong>More Tags: </strong><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/interactive-web-solution/">Website Development Company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/ecommerce-solutions/">ecommerce website design in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/mobile-application-development/">mobile application development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/">best digital marketing services in bangalore</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018/">10 steps website design processes for startup -2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5149</post-id> </item> <item><title>How to use landing pages for your business-2018?</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 10:17:27 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category> <category><![CDATA[advantages of digital marketing]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO agency in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5085</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>How to use landing pages for your business-2018? When you are planning to create a Google AdWords for your business. The landing page is your key chance to convince the customer to convert &#8211; to buy your products, fill out a form or download a resource. You should have high-quality landing pages to optimize conversion [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/">How to use landing pages for your business-2018?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="wp-image-5086 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/how-to-use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=671%2C377&#038;ssl=1" alt="Use landing pages for business, digital marketing company in bangalore" width="671" height="377" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/how-to-use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/how-to-use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 671px) 100vw, 671px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1 style="text-align: justify;">How to use landing pages for your business-2018?</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">When you are planning to create a Google AdWords for your business. The landing page is your key chance to convince the customer to convert &#8211; to buy your products, fill out a form or download a resource. You should have high-quality landing pages to optimize conversion rates, and highly relevant pages will also lower your conversion costs.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Very important quality of an optimized landing page is relevance: Your ad text should be relevant to your keywords, your landing page should be relevant to your Google ad. Landing page with relevant ad text also gets higher quality scores and better ad rankings as a result.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Designing specific landing pages that talk directly to the user&#8217;s search query will have a real impact on your AdWords account and, most importantly, drive more conversions. It’s worth it to devote major time and effort to optimize your AdWords landing pages.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><img class="alignnone wp-image-5087 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business-410x1024.png?resize=652%2C1629&#038;ssl=1" alt="How to use landing pages for your business-2018" width="652" height="1629" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=410%2C1024&amp;ssl=1 410w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=120%2C300&amp;ssl=1 120w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=768%2C1920&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=600%2C1500&amp;ssl=1 600w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?w=800&amp;ssl=1 800w" sizes="(max-width: 652px) 100vw, 652px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Create Optimized Landing Pages for Google AdWords</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Creating AdWords landing pages can be a hard task – there’s a lot to take into consideration. Some challenges of creating AdWords landing pages include:</p><h3 style="text-align: justify;">You can’t build landing pages in AdWords:</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">You can&#8217;t have great AdWords ads for your business without solid landing pages, Google won&#8217;t provide landing page assistance within AdWords. So we need to build landing pages separately.</p><h3 style="text-align: justify;">You need outside help to make landing page:</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Designing landing pages generally <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/">choose the best web design company</a> to edit and manage the pages, that web designer to design the pages and a hosting environment. That means major time and money.</p><h3 style="text-align: justify;">Specific requirements for landing pages:</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">The good landing page has many different elements to consider – your landing pages need to be relevant to your keyword and ads in order to earn a good Quality Score. You also need to have conversion tracking properly set up to track what is and is not working.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Follow the steps to improve your landing page experience:</h2><h3 style="text-align: justify;">1. It should be offer relevant, genuine content and Helpful</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Your landing page should contain direct relevant to your google ads text and keywords.</li><li>Provide specific thing while someone clicks on ads. if someone clicks for a particular bike model, they shouldn&#8217;t get all the bikes on the landing page.</li><li>Provide options when a user wants options. if someone’s looking to compare cars, they probably don&#8217;t want to go specific model page. They expect more.</li><li>Give a useful information about whatever you are advertising</li></ul><h3 style="text-align: justify;">2. Increase transparency and loyalty on your website</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Give proper information about your business and what your business does</li><li>Share everything about your product or services before asking visitors to fill out forms</li><li>Show your contact details to find your visitors easily</li><li>Before asking the personal details of the customers, make it clear why you are asking and what you going to do with it</li></ul><h3 style="text-align: justify;">3. Create mobile and computer navigation easy</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Create and design your page well, so people don’t have to hunt around for information.</li><li>Create the best ads that make the peoples order your product.</li><li>when the customers in your landing page don&#8217;t annoy with pop-ups or other features that interfere with their navigation of your site.</li><li>Help the customers to find what they are really expected.</li></ul><h3 style="text-align: justify;">4. Try to Decrease your landing page loading time</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Make it sure your landing page loads quickly once someone clicks on your ad, whether on a computer or mobile device.</li><li>Consider changing your landing page into an Accelerated Mobile Page (AMP).</li><li>Check your site scores on mobile speed, and get quick fixes to improve it.</li></ul><h2 style="text-align: justify;">The Benefits of Using Video on Landing Pages</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">whenever possible you can use the video on your landing pages. It provides a passive engagement medium where visitors can experience your message with very little effort. If you are using video on landing pages can increase conversion by 80%.</p><h3 style="text-align: justify;">Some reasons why video can lift your landing page conversion rates</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Landing page&#8217;s video increase the length of time and people stay on your landing page for more time, giving your brand message longer to sink in.</li><li>If you feature yourself or company employees in the video, the trust factor is raised significantly.</li><li>Customers are lazy and prefer to watch vs. read.</li></ul><p style="text-align: justify;">Nowadays the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/">advantages of digital marketing</a> are huge so the landing pages are very much useful to attract customers who want to buy your product which one you have shown in google ads. The best landing pages increase the sales and collecting customer’s information. Whenever you are going to run Google AdWords try to create a landing page first. We are here in the market to create good looking and attractive landing page.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Here the Best Digital Marketing Company in Bangalore:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">We are CairoCorps Consulting Private Limited, One of India’s Best <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/">digital marketing company in Bangalore</a>. We are offering comprehensive services to your business such as landing page creation, running the digital marketing campaign, web design, mobile application development and <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/">SEO services in Bangalore</a>.<br /> <strong>Contact us for landing page creation and to run the digital marketing campaign&#8230;</strong></p><p><strong>More Tags: </strong><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/">SEO agency in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/interactive-web-solution/">Web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/ecommerce-solutions/">eCommerce website design in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/mobile-application-development/">Mobile application development company in Bangalore</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/">How to use landing pages for your business-2018?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5085</post-id> </item> <item><title>10 Things to Choose A Best Web Design Company in Bangalore-2018(Infographics)</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 12:46:35 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO company]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5073</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>10 Things to Choose A Best Web Design Company in Bangalore-2018 (Infographics) Present world, the website is a crucial part of your business, even if your business is the small or local business. You have a business then you should hold a website otherwise you can&#8217;t survive in any business. Simply a website is not [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/">10 Things to Choose A Best Web Design Company in Bangalore-2018(Infographics)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class=" wp-image-5074 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/choose-a-web-design-company-in-bangalore-1.png?resize=658%2C370&#038;ssl=1" alt="best web deign compaany in bangalore" width="658" height="370" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/choose-a-web-design-company-in-bangalore-1.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/choose-a-web-design-company-in-bangalore-1.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 658px) 100vw, 658px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1>10 Things to Choose A Best Web Design Company in Bangalore-2018 (Infographics)</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">Present world, the website is a crucial part of your business, even if your business is the small or local business. You have a business then you should hold a website otherwise you can&#8217;t survive in any business. Simply a website is not enough, You must hold a beautiful, professional and eye-catchy website can help your business to attain new heights.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">One of the tremendous tasks to launch new website is choosing a web design company because nowadays huge numbers of web design company are providing comprehensive web solutions across the world. So, web design company seekers have more accountability to choose the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/">best web design company in Bangalore</a>. You will not get any name of the best web design company to contact for website. Here you will consider some points which will assist you in choosing the best company for yourself. If you keep looking for a solution on the web, then there are opportunities that you end up having so many options. And if you try yourself then you may end up having the best and most suitable choice for you.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Before you choose a web design company must consider 10 things which will assist you a lot in determining which company is the suitable for you. Every work needs effort and hard work. Just like this, you also put some efforts into reading 10 things. So, here are 10 things to keep in mind that will help you.</p><p><img class=" wp-image-5075 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/10-things-to-choose-a-web-design-company-in-bangalore-410x1024.png?resize=596%2C1489&#038;ssl=1" alt="10 things to choose a web design company in bangalore" width="596" height="1489" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/10-things-to-choose-a-web-design-company-in-bangalore.png?resize=410%2C1024&amp;ssl=1 410w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/10-things-to-choose-a-web-design-company-in-bangalore.png?resize=120%2C300&amp;ssl=1 120w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/10-things-to-choose-a-web-design-company-in-bangalore.png?resize=768%2C1920&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/10-things-to-choose-a-web-design-company-in-bangalore.png?resize=600%2C1500&amp;ssl=1 600w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/10-things-to-choose-a-web-design-company-in-bangalore.png?w=800&amp;ssl=1 800w" sizes="(max-width: 596px) 100vw, 596px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Reviews are Crucial:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Reviews are crucial to doing your thorough research before concluding the best web design company for your business or project. Check out the reviews and recommendations that are apparently on their website or directly ask them about any other recommendations. According to reviews, you should check first Google reviews then Facebook reviews and others social media reviews besides great social media presence is a good sign of a good web design company. Most of the web design companies in Bangalore are marketing their comprehensive web services on social media sites such as <a href="https://plus.google.com/+CairoCorpsConsulting">Google+</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/cairocorps/" class="broken_link">LinkedIn</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/cairocorps/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/CairoCorps/">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/CairoCorps/">Facebook</a>, and other social media. Social media is a two-way route, it can be an efficient way for a company to sell its products and services and it can also display the plight of the company. In several instances, negative reviews about a company will be visible on all social media pages. By examining the social media pages of all websites, you can understand to ensure that the company doesn&#8217;t have any negative activities with their valuable clients.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Examine Their Portfolios:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Examing at their portfolios that assist you respective web design company has done a lot of projects related to your business will get you a good belief of what they are proficient at doing for you. Make assured to give consideration to the small aspects of their work so that you can tell them what you like or what you don’t like then you will work with them for your business. The best approach to understand any web development company is to see their previous works and portfolios. Once you see their portfolios of live websites, you can be more than convinced of their expertise level. But never hope on the screenshots of the homepages of the portfolios. Ask them to provide you with the live sites up to five which are they developed. Take your time to have a thorough look at the portfolios and visit the respective sites and roam around every page and see if there is anything you have found wrong. You can get clarifications from respective companies about the flaw you have seen. If the purpose for that glitch is client requirement, then alright, but if not, you should try the names of other companies.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Check Their Experience:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Every year, huge numbers of new design companies begin their interactive web solutions in Bangalore. You can&#8217;t believe some overnight web design company that probably won&#8217;t be around in a year to help your new website. If you believe the website development firm you have hired will be the best for you just because they have developed websites dedicatedly for the industry which serves long times. Having many people with various skill sets are working on your website so they can ensure that the website is developed in the best way. Just like building a house, there are various tasks and skill sets needed to complete them. All of the designers pitching in together creates a final website that is more efficient than a website designed by just one person.</p><p style="text-align: left;"><img class="wp-image-5076 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/web-design-company.png?resize=608%2C342&#038;ssl=1" alt="web design company in bangalore" width="608" height="342" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/web-design-company.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/web-design-company.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 608px) 100vw, 608px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Get Their Packages:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Before choosing a website design company, You can decide your budget after the budget will determine whether you will choose a company. Prices are an essential thing while choosing a good web designing company. Remember one point, that is whatever you invest, that should turn into a profit making business. Every web development companies have some packages so get well-known about packages. When approaches to website design, just like anything else, you get what you pay for. Avoid making costs just to save a dollar, especially when you risk losing the long-term value of the results you thought for in the first step. Check out whether the company has any indication of the value given to a business through solid results besides, you have to understand that when a web design company charges incredibly low amount for a bigger project, it is not viable enough. A particular level of expertise will definitely come with a cost.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Communicate with Responsible Person:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Communicate with the responsible person whoever or whichever individual or organization you choose to get your website development, assure that they are interested in communication where you can openly communicate your ideas. In the first stage, it is nearly difficult to determine how future communication will be. Still, you can see it during the first conversation or make business communication. A professional web design company is always polite, listen to our ideas and offers their ideas for resolving a particular problem. It will be helpful to ask how the web development process is going on. besides, notice whether they have local knowledge which is necessary for your project and business to prosper. They must have a clear idea of who your audience is and what kind of <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/">digital marketing services in Bangalore</a> can help you which needs to be incorporated into the website&#8217;s design. You can quickly find some web design company anywhere in the world and Bangalore but you aware what types of web solutions they provide and they have the basic knowledge these are crucial.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">24/7 Maintenance and Customer Support:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Every business needs 24/7 maintenance and customer support because any time and anything happen your website. For companies that provide you with a dedicated point of contact or support, that person or responsible person might always be available 24/7 of the week. That style a company handles their clients is often a significant example of the way they run their business and develop their products. Do assure you find a company who will take your calls, emails and makes updates to your website quickly. You can regularly tell if the company serves quickly by how fast they return your estimate request, but remember, an estimate request for a custom website may take some time to put together. Subsequent all, they are human, and seldom they become sick, take vacations, or have to take care of their personal lives. In that time if your point of contact isn’t available, you need alternative a person or a team who can give you the support so an alternative point of contact needs to get while agreement sign.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Know Responsive Web Design:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Responsive website development is not a trend, it is just the best system to design a website these days. Because Nowadays high internet access occurs on mobile devices compared to desktop. If a company isn’t completely knowledgeable in responsive design or recommends you that separate mobile website would be a better option, You can hunt another best company. By this, responsive website design is mandatory for any website development. The company that you choose should have a portfolio that demonstrates experience in designing and developing responsive websites. While choosing your <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/interactive-web-solution/">website development company in Bangalore</a>, check their client&#8217;s websites on a mobile device so you can assess their work for yourself. check the websites are suitable for various screen sizes or optimized for across various device.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Analyze their Creativity:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Before you go hunting for someone to design your website, you should check their past website to see their creativity, innovative and ideas you also need to share some idea of how to present it to your web design company. You can make a list of a few websites you admire and why you do, perhaps for their workflow maybe for their role. That will assist the designers to know your ideas and taste. If a company does not admit to your ideas, then you probably don&#8217;t them handling your job. While it&#8217;s necessary for the company to listen to you. Your website requires to be designed by one who knows design and can bring exciting ideas to the table. when they applied creativity and innovative it should be related to your business that is necessary.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Office Location:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Huge numbers of companies have developed websites online and it does really matter where they are in Bangalore or across the world. Excellent services with fair price would be a full score for you. Web design companies establish credibility based on their existing customers, which means that you can see their previous work and decide if they are suitable for your needs. Still, Do sure the company location of your option doesn&#8217;t have a location where you can meet with them if necessary. Knowing where your web design company is based will also assist further restrict any deception that could occur with the respective company.</p><p><img class="wp-image-5077 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/choose-a-web-design-company-in-bangalore.png?resize=626%2C352&#038;ssl=1" alt="website development company in bangalore" width="626" height="352" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/choose-a-web-design-company-in-bangalore.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/choose-a-web-design-company-in-bangalore.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 626px) 100vw, 626px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: left;">SEO Compatible Website:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">A plenty of effort puts into building a website, besides effort goes into optimizing it, promoting it, measuring its performance, and making improvements. Today businesses are fully based on digital marketing so you need to build your website Search Engine Optimization(SEO) friendly its assist you a lot in future. Check whether has a digital marketing team ready to take over every aspect of digital marketing while the new website is developing, choose for a web design company that also concentrates in digital marketing and <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/">SEO services in Bangalore</a> so before choosing a company try to get SEO friendly websites.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Ready to Choose the Best web design company in Bangalore:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">At CairoCorps Consulting, we are offering comprehensive solutions to your business such as web design, e-commerce web design digital marketing, SEO services, and <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/mobile-application-development/">mobile application development in Bangalore</a> and across the world. What gives us different is our consultative approach and deep professional and technical skills. we analyze your requirements initially then we build website regarding your ideas and our creativity. Prices are affordable and have many packages.<br /> <strong>Forgot one more thing to tell you to <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/contact/">contact us</a> !!!</strong></p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/">10 Things to Choose A Best Web Design Company in Bangalore-2018(Infographics)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5073</post-id> </item> </channel> </rss>