<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
><channel><title>seo company in bangalore &#8211; CairoCorps Consulting</title> <atom:link href="https://cairocorps.com/tag/seo-company-in-bangalore/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><link>https://cairocorps.com</link> <description>Creations &#124; Digital Transformations</description> <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 10:31:14 +0000</lastBuildDate> <language>en-US</language> <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod> <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency><image> <url>https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/ccc-logo-1.png?fit=25%2C32&#038;ssl=1</url><title>seo company in bangalore &#8211; CairoCorps Consulting</title><link>https://cairocorps.com</link> <width>32</width> <height>32</height> </image> <site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">142080933</site> <item><title>YouTube Outage In 2018</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 07:22:24 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[seo company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web development company in banglore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5252</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>YouTube Outage In 2018 YouTube is top social media for videos in worldwide it&#8217;s running successfully with lakhs of subscriber and channel. In these YouTube, YouTube TV, and YouTube music down around one hour then it&#8217;s back on Wednesday (16/10/2018). As per web development company in Bangalore, we discuss what happened YouTube around one hour [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/">YouTube Outage In 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="size-full wp-image-5253 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/youtube-outage-2018.jpg?resize=759%2C422&#038;ssl=1" alt="YouTube outage 2018, web design company in Bangalore" width="759" height="422" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/youtube-outage-2018.jpg?w=759&amp;ssl=1 759w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/youtube-outage-2018.jpg?resize=300%2C167&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/youtube-outage-2018.jpg?resize=600%2C334&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 759px) 100vw, 759px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1>YouTube Outage In 2018</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">YouTube is top social media for videos in worldwide it&#8217;s running successfully with lakhs of subscriber and channel. In these YouTube, YouTube TV, and YouTube music down around one hour then it&#8217;s back on Wednesday (16/10/2018). As per <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web development company in Bangalore</a>, we discuss what happened YouTube around one hour and how it was rectified.</p><h2>what happened YouTube</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">A lot of users has reported regards getting &#8220;500 internal server error&#8221; on him/her display. In this global outrage was happened across the world and user was reported continuously from across the world because unable to access or upload content on YouTube. YouTube was felt a major outage in that history. Users across the world began to notice that the video service’s sites and mobile application were down around 9:20 PM ET, and everything continues inaccessible more than an hour later. YouTube TV and YouTube Music are also affected by the service interruption.</p><p><img class="size-full wp-image-5254 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_2.png?resize=761%2C406&#038;ssl=1" alt="YouTube outrage 2018, web development company in bangalore" width="761" height="406" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_2.png?w=761&amp;ssl=1 761w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_2.png?resize=300%2C160&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_2.png?resize=600%2C320&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 761px) 100vw, 761px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2>YouTube team had rectified the issue:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">After getting a lot of reports from users, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCC32iZBJCrDJONbYRlLiW0A" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a> has confirmed the global outage in a tweet. “We’re working on resolving this and will let you know once fixed,” besides the Team YouTube account says. “We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause and will keep you updated.” Since of 10.35PM ET, the account is still responding to reports of the global outage saying that the team is working on the problem.</p><p><img class="size-full wp-image-5255 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_3.png?resize=676%2C270&#038;ssl=1" alt="YouTube issue in 2018, best web design company in bangalore" width="676" height="270" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_3.png?w=676&amp;ssl=1 676w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_3.png?resize=300%2C120&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_3.png?resize=600%2C240&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 676px) 100vw, 676px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><p style="text-align: justify;">YouTube&#8217;s technical team was working to find the issue of down on YouTube. Finally, the team was found an issue that is the server and YouTube team has rectified the server issue. YouTube&#8217;s global outage was lasting around one hour. Finally, YouTube asked sorry to all users through <a href="https://twitter.com/CairoCorps" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a>. Now YouTube is running successfully all over the world.</p><p><img class="size-full wp-image-5256 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?resize=793%2C357&#038;ssl=1" alt="YouTube problem, website development company in bangalore" width="793" height="357" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?w=793&amp;ssl=1 793w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?resize=300%2C135&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?resize=768%2C346&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.in/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?resize=600%2C270&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 793px) 100vw, 793px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/">YouTube Outage In 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5252</post-id> </item> <item><title>Why Digital Marketing is Important in 2018?</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 07:27:48 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO agency in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[seo company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5185</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Why digital marketing is important in 2018? Marketing is the backbone of every business in the world without marketing you never succeed in your respective business. Marketing is how you sell a product when customers need the explanation of awesome products. The present reality is that promoting sales at the intersection of the business, therefore, [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/">Why Digital Marketing is Important in 2018?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="wp-image-5186 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important.png?resize=594%2C334&#038;ssl=1" alt="why digital marketing is important" width="594" height="334" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 594px) 100vw, 594px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1 style="text-align: left;">Why digital marketing is important in 2018?</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">Marketing is the backbone of every business in the world without marketing you never succeed in your respective business. Marketing is how you sell a product when customers need the explanation of awesome products. The present reality is that promoting sales at the intersection of the business, therefore, the client – the good arbiter of the self-interests of the business and therefore the wants of the customer. Current days have two main marketing that includes online marketing and digital marketing. Here I write elaborately why digital marketing important in 2018. Once you read you will get more about digital marketing.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">What is Digital Marketing</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Promoting products or services or brands through several forms of digital technology that is digital marketing. For example, advertising mediums that might be used as part of the digital marketing strategy of a business could include promotional endeavors performed through the internet, social media, mobile phones, and computerized billboards. Similar to any form of marketing, the goal of digital marketing is to promote and sell a product or service. Further, the purpose of digital marketing is to connect a business or company with its target audience through several digital marketing strategies such as Search Engine Optimization(SEO), Pay Per Click(PPC), Social Media Marketing(SMM), Social Media Optimization(SMO), Newsletter Campaign and bulk SMS, and etc&#8230;</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Why digital marketing is important</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Digital marketing is most important marketing in the world because it is not only a quickly growing force in the contemporary marketing playing area but also it is set to be the future of every business, and it appears probable that digital marketing will quickly replace all types of offline marketing forms altogether because <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">advantages of digital marketing</a> is huge. While earlier generations will no doubt regret the decease of paper-based newspapers, books, communication methods, and conventional TV advertisements and radio broadcasts, those who have grown up with the internet penetration and mobile phones penetration are already covering the bright new world of digital marketing. The realities are that digital marketing methods of transmission and marketing are so fast besides cost-effective, more adaptable, efficient and modernized, so it is possibly unsurprising that once the new technology became accessible we started quickly moving into the new technology then only digital marketing so important for every business.</p><p><img class="wp-image-5187 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018.png?resize=597%2C336&#038;ssl=1" alt="" width="597" height="336" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 597px) 100vw, 597px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2>7 Important of Digital Marketing</h2><p>Here you can read seven reasons being to why digital marketing is important in 2018.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">1. The whole World Well Connected With Internet</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Why digital marketing is booming, well the whole world there are several factors associated or responsible for digital marketing growth. Besides one of the importance of digital marketing is the whole world well connected to the internet because of the cheap internet and mobile users increased. We have been seeing the difference in communication since the arrival of the internet. The Internet has undoubtedly changed the way of purchasing and communicating with the people. Everything has become the fast-paced and getting people more laziness since whatever you want just gives up at your doorstep with just one click. These are the reason for digital marketing is booming and the importance of digital marketing in 2018 and upcoming years.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">2. Customers are Online</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">People believe online as a way to cut costs and cut time. E-commerce shops assist customers of travel time and retailers of storefront costs so buyers are roaming always the internet to buy something. People rarely consider the costs that online shopping adds to their transaction. The distance between the buyer and seller adds risks to the customers plate. If youre part of an E-commerce business, the takeaway is this risks. In lightweight of this, associate degree service an e-commerce merchant will offer to ease the psychological feature prices of looking online will increase the customer’s perceived price of the merchandise. Today people are roaming the internet and customers are always online that is why digital marketing is important in 2018.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">3. Competitors are Online</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Competitors were gone beyond you in business Its sign of digital marketing adoption. Literally, most of the businesses are using digital marketing. Each year more and more businesses give up offline marketing methods and focus on SEO, Google Adwords or social media spending large money on these marketing. This is the explanation for why the market gets progressively competitive and large players to get prior to very little firms. As little business on the market, you can&#8217;t vie with them, however, there&#8217;s one thing you&#8217;ll do. you&#8217;ll use Google Alerts tool to observe your competitors. This tool can enable you to trace your competitors&#8217; product and selling methods in order that you&#8217;ll learn one thing from them and improve your own business strategy. Competitors are online so immediately hunt a best digital marketing company.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">4. Cost-effective Marketing</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">One of the importance of digital marketing is more cost-effective while comparing other offline marketing. This is especially essential for startups and small business. Digital marketing is savvier than offline marketing. This is particularly vital for independent companies as they don&#8217;t have numerous assets or a considerable measure of capital. New media can furnish you with a less expensive and more compelling publicizing digital marketing company channel. In digital marketing has many types of marketing according to your budget you can choose the suitable strategies. <img class="alignnone wp-image-5188 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/Feature_Image_Mobile_Device_Management_BYOD_Evolution.jpg?resize=630%2C295&#038;ssl=1" alt="why digital marketing is important" width="630" height="295" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/Feature_Image_Mobile_Device_Management_BYOD_Evolution.jpg?w=600&amp;ssl=1 600w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/Feature_Image_Mobile_Device_Management_BYOD_Evolution.jpg?resize=300%2C141&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 630px) 100vw, 630px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h3 style="text-align: left;">5. Cater to the Mobile Consumer</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">No doubt, Digital marketing has evolved such a lot that mobile devices are not any longer thought-about mere alternatives to private computers or laptops. Without any doubt, with the fast expansion of smartphones, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mobile_marketing" target="_blank" rel="noopener">mobile marketing</a> is the most contemporary way of data dispersal that is also today’s basic correspondence channel. Smartphones have transformed into the main part of our life that most of the grown-ups in India dependably have their mobile devices within their reaching distance. The greatest gathering of customers is using their cell phones day by day, so it&#8217;s basic that you utilize a marketing arrangement that objectives these mobile gadgets suitably.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">6. Highly Adaptable Marketing</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Importance of digital marketing is changing is that it needs digital marketers to be equally willing to vary and adapt. Flexibility, therefore, is a necessary quality during a digital promoting skilled, as a result of you usually ought to be ready to adopt new practices, update your ability set and knowledge domain, sustain with business best practices, and keep current with the newest technologies and trends. an excellent example of however things area unit perpetually dynamic in digital promoting is that the Google formula. The formula is often being updated, and each time they unharness a replacement version, it changes the means digital marketers and <a href="https://moz.com/learn/seo/what-is-seo" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEO</a> specialists approach their craft.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">7. Most of the People Shopping Online</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">A recent research has exposed that over 120 million Indian people are expected to buy the products or services through online this year. In the previous year of study exposed that as many as 108 million consumers did online shopping on mobile phones. Mobile phones are becoming the favored choice of device for e-commerce businesses. The research also highlighted a flood in the number of customers shopping on smartphones across India and the world with tier II and III cities are increasing trends.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Best Digital Marketing Company in Bangalore</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">CairoCorps Consulting is one of a best <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing company in Bangalore</a> who takes care of clients and feel their pain provide the best digital marketing of their business put their business at top of the competition despite any industry. The organization is also holding professional experts on the latest technologies of digital marketing with very comprehensive solutions.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>You have any suggestion about this blog let us know through comments&#8230;</strong></p><p><strong>More Tags:</strong> <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEO agency in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/interactive-web-solution/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing services in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/ecommerce-solutions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">e-commerce development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/mobile-application-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">e-commerce development company in Bangalore</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: left;"><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/">Why Digital Marketing is Important in 2018?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5185</post-id> </item> </channel> </rss>