<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
><channel><title>CairoCorps Consulting</title> <atom:link href="https://cairocorps.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><link>https://cairocorps.com</link> <description>Creations &#124; Digital Transformations</description> <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 10:31:14 +0000</lastBuildDate> <language>en-US</language> <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod> <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency><image> <url>https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/ccc-logo-1.png?fit=25%2C32&#038;ssl=1</url><title>CairoCorps Consulting</title><link>https://cairocorps.com</link> <width>32</width> <height>32</height> </image> <site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">142080933</site> <item><title>Content Management System Used by Web Design Company</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/content-management-system-used-by-web-design-company/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/content-management-system-used-by-web-design-company/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 11:23:26 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web designers in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web development company Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5288</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Content Management System Used by Web Design Company Welcome to the Modern world with amazing technologies. Most of the time peoples busy using technologies. Everyone expecting everything in their hand. Even technology gave that too. nowadays everyone having some kind of gadgets in their pockets. It&#8217;s entirely changed their life. They look at the online [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/content-management-system-used-by-web-design-company/">Content Management System Used by Web Design Company</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure id="attachment_5290" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="size-large wp-image-5290" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-Used-by-Web-Design-Company-1024x512.jpg?resize=1024%2C512&#038;ssl=1" alt="Content Management System Used by Web Design Company" width="1024" height="512" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-Used-by-Web-Design-Company.jpg?w=1024&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-Used-by-Web-Design-Company.jpg?resize=300%2C150&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-Used-by-Web-Design-Company.jpg?resize=768%2C384&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-Used-by-Web-Design-Company.jpg?resize=700%2C350&amp;ssl=1 700w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-Used-by-Web-Design-Company.jpg?resize=600%2C300&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Content Management System Used by Web Design Company</figcaption></figure><h1>Content Management System Used by Web Design Company</h1><p>Welcome to the Modern world with amazing technologies. Most of the time peoples busy using technologies. Everyone expecting everything in their hand. Even technology gave that too. nowadays everyone having some kind of gadgets in their pockets. It&#8217;s entirely changed their life. They look at the online and get to know which services, products are the best in the market. If someone has a website for his or her business is giving more return to them for making more business and more money. Attracting and powerful websites giving more traffic to your websites. More traffic more business. Hope you much heard about content management system. For creating attracting website choose the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com">best web designing company</a>. CairoCorps is One of the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com">best website developers in Bangalore</a></p><p>Create and maintaining a website is an overwhelming task for every business when we don’t have much knowledge in the content management system and don’t have a web development team. But the most defective thing is outdated information’s can cost a company in many ways. The good solution we need to maintain the website will depend on good CMS.</p><p>All the websites come with a content management system. It means we have full access to modify the content, images and all at day and night. Just log in to the website and do the changes on our own. All the websites come with an ample amount of training so don’t worry about it. Mostly we are using WordPress, Joomla, Magento or Drupal. These are all the most effective Content Management Systems in the current periods.</p><p>&nbsp;</p><h2>Content Management System (CMS)</h2><p>&nbsp;</p><p>CMS is a web application that makes us modify the content and images easily. No need of any technical knowledge for access this. The user can easily build websites, streamline the web publishing procedure and deployed easily. We can create content-rich websites. Many open source CMS look easier but technically its need more development effort, they work on it and deploy it and customize the website. Then only they will create a suitable CMS for your requirements.</p><p>Cairocorps CMS developers have vast expertise in a lot of CMS platforms. So they will give a good solution for all your requirements. they build amazing websites and CMS. If you need any content management system requirements to ask India’s Largest <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com">web development company in Bangalore</a>. Learn more about web development <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com">click here</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Cairocorps have large of experience to develop websites and web applications, they also use most of the Open Source  Content Management Systems like Joomla!, WordPress, Mambo, Drupal, osCommerce, DotNetNuke and Pligg CMS. Pick your suitable one for your business</p><h3>Brief about Content Management Systems</h3><p>The website design is no longer limited to static HTML pages. Nowadays businesses have to deal with daily basis so the information’s are increasing daily. Updating a static site is taking more time, we need to enter the coding part and change the contents if we do this definitely we need to know some technical knowledge. Its take much time and a lot of manpower required. This what we are using a content management system.it gives the solution without wasting any time and not needed any technical knowledge as well.</p> <figure id="attachment_5291" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com"><img class="wp-image-5291 size-large" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System-1024x732.jpg?resize=1024%2C732&#038;ssl=1" alt="best website developers in Bangalore" width="1024" height="732" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System.jpg?resize=1024%2C732&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System.jpg?resize=300%2C214&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System.jpg?resize=768%2C549&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System.jpg?resize=1140%2C814&amp;ssl=1 1140w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Content-Management-System.jpg?resize=600%2C429&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">best website developers in Bangalore</figcaption></figure><p>A content management system (<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Content_management_system">CMS</a>) handles all your dynamic content and website needs from an easy to use backend solution. CMS developed websites are easy to maintain, update with better and simple control panel. Which ultimately amplified your productivity and most importantly you don&#8217;t have to be technically professional to do required changes.</p><p>CMS handles all the dynamic contents and websites needs from back-end solution. CMS makes the websites are easy to use and maintain, updates with better and simple control panel. It obviously increases productivity and definitely, you don’t need any technical knowledge to change the website contents. We can update daily basis.</p><p>If your business running by using a simple static website don’t worry switch your website as a dynamic one. Are you looking for a technical person support daily for changing the content means it is a huge burden? Take a good step to move into a Dynamic website with cairocorps. Dynamic websites have come with a lot of highly functional, responsive web design and Content Management System too.</p><p>Know something about <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites/">Static and Dynamic website differents</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><h3>Companies provide the following CMS design and development services.</h3><ul><li>Web content management services</li><li>Component content management systems</li><li>Enterprise content management systems</li><li>Corporate CMS</li><li>Joomla Development</li><li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WordPress">WordPress</a> Design and Integration</li><li>Magneto ecommerce CMS</li></ul><h3></h3><h3>Why companies are giving more preference to CMS than other website development services?</h3><p>Some of the given features make the companies choose CMS. It gives more features. Have a look below</p><ul><li>SEO friendly website – Search engine perform in a friendly way good for user and search engines, If our websites are supported SEO we can do some Search engine Optimizing works and come first in the search engines. Its automatically give more business and growth.</li><li>Multiple languages – If we run the business all over the world we should keep the website in multiple languages. Then only our customers join with us easily. So we should provide the languages by their location, Its possible in Dynamic websites.</li><li>Social Media Integrations – We can make our website as social friendly which gives more useful things. We can fully leverage of leading social platform like facebook, twitter and lot more. If we are more active in social media it also gives more business. Ask how</li><li>Customization &#8211; Customization is one of the best features comes with CMS developed websites. We don’t worry about the updates coming in future.</li></ul><p>Cairocorps is one of the leading <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com">web design company in Bangalore</a>. we create full fledge CMS enabled websites and we give proper training to update the content and images by your own. We give an effective content management system with full features. Please contact us to know more about our open source Content Management Systems.</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/content-management-system-used-by-web-design-company/">Content Management System Used by Web Design Company</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/content-management-system-used-by-web-design-company/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5288</post-id> </item> <item><title>Importance of Web Design</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/importance-of-web-design/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/importance-of-web-design/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 06:22:23 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web development company Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5265</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Importance of Web Design The current day a lot of businessmen is spending huge money on their web design process and digital marketing. Behind this have many reasons I found some businessmen they are running their business through the website only that is why they are spending huge money on website design process besides they [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/importance-of-web-design/">Importance of Web Design</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="size-large wp-image-5266 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Importance-of-Web-Design-1024x512.png?resize=1024%2C512&#038;ssl=1" alt="Importance of Web Design, website design company" width="1024" height="512" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Importance-of-Web-Design.png?w=1024&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Importance-of-Web-Design.png?resize=300%2C150&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Importance-of-Web-Design.png?resize=768%2C384&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Importance-of-Web-Design.png?resize=700%2C350&amp;ssl=1 700w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Importance-of-Web-Design.png?resize=600%2C300&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1><span style="font-size: xx-large;"><b>Importance of Web Design</b></span></h1><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The current day a lot of businessmen is spending huge money on their web design process and digital marketing. Behind this have many reasons I found some businessmen they are running their business through the website only that is why they are spending huge money on website design process besides they are spending huge money on digital marketing includes SEO, PPC, Bulk SMS, newsletter campaigns and etc&#8230; In this article, I am going to discuss the importance of web design for business, blogger, NGOs, and anything.<br /> While we come to highlight your online presence, If you run a business or sell a service or product, it is highly paramount that the quality and prices of respective products or services. Importance of web design is based on the penetration of smartphone, computer, internet, and electronic devices there are many things that you want to put into great consideration. Anything does this really indicate to online marketers? Fundamentally, the act of building your online presence in the market does not simply finish by just designing a basic website for your business or company. besides, you must adopt some digital marketing strategy includes SEO, PPC, SMM, Bulk SMS, and newsletter campaign to boost your business. We are considering the only website is the main tool of digital marketing that is without website we cant move further that is all.<br /> We can see today a lot of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Startup_company" target="_blank" rel="noopener">startups</a> striving to build their foot in the market. Nevertheless, it is a painful fact that several of them lose to reach as much targeted audience as they expect in the first place. Which brings them for losing? It is mainly because they undervalue the capability of a created website to earn business for them. Website development for startups plans can demonstrate very fruitful. You must consider your website should be an asset. Let us look at some of the important reasons why a website is important for business growth.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: large;"><b>Some of The Importance of Web Design</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">As a businessman, you must to know where are your customers. There are various factors that lead to a successful online presence in the market. But before going on any further, let’s know first How exactly important web design is it?</span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: medium;"><b><span style="font-size: large;">24/7 Accessibility</span></b></span></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">When we arrive up with a startup or business plan and initially Everyone establishes a physical office or store for your company, through that you might get audience throughout the daytime or when you are there. People are quite busy with their daily life So, Visiting Your office is not possible for everyone. If you hold a website for your business strategy as an online forum, there is a huge chance of getting a lot of audiences online to link up with you. This has happened because people are piped up with internet in day and night. People prefer to get into everything the easy way with good quality is possible. Your website has some content with all the basic information and data. They will be able to access website 24/7.</span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-family: brandon-grotesque, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: large;">Increase in Mobile Usage</span></span></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-family: brandon-grotesque, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: medium;">All studies are come out regards mobile usages of today reflected huge increasing trends. It is proving a real surge in mobile usage. The usability of 4G has also influenced how people use their mobile devices. then, it was reported that two-thirds of people had a smartphone, with most of the internet users admitting their smartphone was the most important device for going online. All are spent twice as long online on our smartphones than laptops or personal computers. Many studies are demonstrating </span><span style="font-family: brandon-grotesque, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: medium;">just how many people browse on their smartphones and tablets instead of a laptop or desktop computer. This highlighted an exciting turn in smartphone users so through a <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web design company</a> to get a responsive website immediately.</span></span></span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><strong><span style="font-family: brandon-grotesque, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: large;">Penetration of Internet</span></span></strong></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-family: brandon-grotesque, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Above half of the world’s people is now online, with the latest study revealing that almost a quarter of a billion new internet users came online for the first time in 2017. While comparing in India&#8217;s metropolitan cities around 80% of people using internet some of the studies are showing this results so this is a good time to go online otherwise never survive in your business to choose the best <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/">digital marketing company</a> for your business.</span></span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-family: walkway ultraboldregular, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: large;">Search Engine Optimization</span></span></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-family: brandon-grotesque, sans-serif;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Over 650 million websites and another 51 million added each year, there is huge online competition for your services or products. We looked at several ways to make your website stand out aesthetically, but there are also ways to help it stand out on search engines. Search engine visibility is very important to your website because most of the businessmen are getting leads through google&#8217;s visibility. Being on the first page of search engine search for your services is crucial to your online conversions. <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Search_engine_optimization">Search Engine Optimization</a> (SEO) is which assist your website rank well with search engines. Hire is an <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/seo-company-in-bangalore/">SEO company</a> that can be performed SEO services on your website. An important factor you should consider when developing a website it should SEO friendly websites.</span></span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: large;"><b>Looking for Web Design Company in Bangalore?</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">These are some of the importance of web design for your business. Web design is not just designing a good looking website, it should be user-friendly. a website is an asset of your business If you are not having a website <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/">contact us </a>for prices. you have any suggestion regarding this post let us know&#8230;</span></p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/importance-of-web-design/">Importance of Web Design</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/importance-of-web-design/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5265</post-id> </item> <item><title>YouTube Outage In 2018</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 07:22:24 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Trending]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[seo company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web development company in banglore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5252</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>YouTube Outage In 2018 YouTube is top social media for videos in worldwide it&#8217;s running successfully with lakhs of subscriber and channel. In these YouTube, YouTube TV, and YouTube music down around one hour then it&#8217;s back on Wednesday (16/10/2018). As per web development company in Bangalore, we discuss what happened YouTube around one hour [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/">YouTube Outage In 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="size-full wp-image-5253 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/youtube-outage-2018.jpg?resize=759%2C422&#038;ssl=1" alt="YouTube outage 2018, web design company in Bangalore" width="759" height="422" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/youtube-outage-2018.jpg?w=759&amp;ssl=1 759w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/youtube-outage-2018.jpg?resize=300%2C167&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/youtube-outage-2018.jpg?resize=600%2C334&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 759px) 100vw, 759px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1>YouTube Outage In 2018</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">YouTube is top social media for videos in worldwide it&#8217;s running successfully with lakhs of subscriber and channel. In these YouTube, YouTube TV, and YouTube music down around one hour then it&#8217;s back on Wednesday (16/10/2018). As per <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web development company in Bangalore</a>, we discuss what happened YouTube around one hour and how it was rectified.</p><h2>what happened YouTube</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">A lot of users has reported regards getting &#8220;500 internal server error&#8221; on him/her display. In this global outrage was happened across the world and user was reported continuously from across the world because unable to access or upload content on YouTube. YouTube was felt a major outage in that history. Users across the world began to notice that the video service’s sites and mobile application were down around 9:20 PM ET, and everything continues inaccessible more than an hour later. YouTube TV and YouTube Music are also affected by the service interruption.</p><p><img class="size-full wp-image-5254 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_2.png?resize=761%2C406&#038;ssl=1" alt="YouTube outrage 2018, web development company in bangalore" width="761" height="406" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_2.png?w=761&amp;ssl=1 761w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_2.png?resize=300%2C160&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_2.png?resize=600%2C320&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 761px) 100vw, 761px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2>YouTube team had rectified the issue:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">After getting a lot of reports from users, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCC32iZBJCrDJONbYRlLiW0A" target="_blank" rel="noopener">YouTube</a> has confirmed the global outage in a tweet. “We’re working on resolving this and will let you know once fixed,” besides the Team YouTube account says. “We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause and will keep you updated.” Since of 10.35PM ET, the account is still responding to reports of the global outage saying that the team is working on the problem.</p><p><img class="size-full wp-image-5255 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_3.png?resize=676%2C270&#038;ssl=1" alt="YouTube issue in 2018, best web design company in bangalore" width="676" height="270" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_3.png?w=676&amp;ssl=1 676w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_3.png?resize=300%2C120&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_3.png?resize=600%2C240&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 676px) 100vw, 676px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><p style="text-align: justify;">YouTube&#8217;s technical team was working to find the issue of down on YouTube. Finally, the team was found an issue that is the server and YouTube team has rectified the server issue. YouTube&#8217;s global outage was lasting around one hour. Finally, YouTube asked sorry to all users through <a href="https://twitter.com/CairoCorps" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Twitter</a>. Now YouTube is running successfully all over the world.</p><p><img class="size-full wp-image-5256 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?resize=793%2C357&#038;ssl=1" alt="YouTube problem, website development company in bangalore" width="793" height="357" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?w=793&amp;ssl=1 793w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?resize=300%2C135&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?resize=768%2C346&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Screenshot_4.png?resize=600%2C270&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 793px) 100vw, 793px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/">YouTube Outage In 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/youtube-outage-in-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5252</post-id> </item> <item><title>Web Design Company in Nagercoil</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/web-design-company-in-nagercoil/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/web-design-company-in-nagercoil/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 10:53:29 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web development company Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO agency in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in nagercoil]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5235</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Web Design Company in Nagercoil CairoCorps Consulting is a top web design company and providing comprehensive web design solutions to startups, small enterprises, NGOs and etc. Looking at a web design company in Nagercoil, CairoCorps Consulting is providing web design, digital marketing, and SEO services to all types of business. A website is a very [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/web-design-company-in-nagercoil/">Web Design Company in Nagercoil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="size-large wp-image-5236 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Web-Design-company-in-Nagercoil-1024x512.png?resize=1024%2C512&#038;ssl=1" alt="Web Design Company in Nagercoil, web development company in nagercoil" width="1024" height="512" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Web-Design-company-in-Nagercoil.png?w=1024&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Web-Design-company-in-Nagercoil.png?resize=300%2C150&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Web-Design-company-in-Nagercoil.png?resize=768%2C384&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Web-Design-company-in-Nagercoil.png?resize=700%2C350&amp;ssl=1 700w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Web-Design-company-in-Nagercoil.png?resize=600%2C300&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1>Web Design Company in Nagercoil</h1><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">CairoCorps Consulting is a top web design company and providing comprehensive web design solutions to startups, small enterprises, NGOs and etc. Looking at a web design company in Nagercoil, CairoCorps Consulting is providing web design, digital marketing, and SEO services to all types of business. A website is a very popular aspect that any business It makes your business an influential in online. If you own a website, it gives a brand image for your business in order to reach out to a multitude of people. It is the first thing people check for to know more about your business and only when it is attractive and authentic that you will get more traffic and leads. We score high in terms of creativity and quality and as a leading web design company in Nagercoil, Position Matters promises to give exemplary design services with customized ideas matching your business goals and services. Here you can check our services.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: large;">Services of Our Web Design Company in Nagercoil</span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Beginning with the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_page" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web pages</a>, template concepts there are many elements that together support to create a premium website. Experienced web design company play a vital role in designing an elegant yet user-friendly website. We can design a variety for our business when you talk about your business and then show the website and explain your services. People will be surprised and they can always refer to your website anytime in the future. Moving an expert in web design services, we understand presentations matters in online and a website should have the basic web design essential parameters along with easy navigation options so that people find your business website interesting, informative with clutter-free designs and our services are given below.</span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: large;">Website Design</span></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">We are leading Website Design and Development with experience in designing and developing interactive websites such as static website, dynamic website, landing pages, e-commerce website, web portal and etc. We offer innovative and imperative web design in compliance with recent technical and business demands over several domains to its global clients. The designing website through custom code as well Content Management System(CMS) besides we have dedicated and skilled team to design your dream website.</span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: large;">Website Maintenance</span></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Our web development team also take care of your valuable website for maintenance and revamping with the latest techniques. we maintain and revamp any type of website which was made by any languages and content management systems. Our dedicated team maintains and revamps very effective at affordable prices.</span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: large;">24/7 Support</span></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">We are providing 24/7 customer support to all our valuable clients whatever services ongoing it will be website designing or digital marketing or SEO services. Our customer support team always assist you on time whatever support you have needed. 24/7 customer support is a kind of support that is available throughout the day, 7 days a week and 365 days a year. The technical service is available around the clock and produces such a seamless assistance, various methods are adopted.</span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: large;">Cheap Price</span></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">If anybody is looking for a cheap web designer in Nagercoil to design your valuable website with good services, you can confidently hire it to handle by Bangalore web developers. We are not just good at work, but very responsible and can be trusted also prices also very cheap. We are offering the qualities everyone wanted and needed so you get it sure. Look at <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website design company in Bangalore</a> for your business developments.</span></p><h3 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: large;">Other Services</span></h3><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">We have a specialized team for not only website design but also digital marketing and mobile application Some of the services includes active static websites, Content Managment System(CMS), dynamic website solution, SEO services, digital marketing, landing page development, search engine optimized website development, newsletter campaign, Pay Per Click (PPC) and bulk SMS. We continuously attempt to reform the way you conduct your day-to-day business by delivering innovative, creative web design services and web application products.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: large;">About CairoCorps Consulting</span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">CairoCorps is <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website development company in Bangalore</a> as well worldwide and strongly believe in educating, empowering and equipping Small and Medium businesses whether it&#8217;s in Bangalore and worldwide we will make a huge difference to their profits through interactive web solutions and digital marketing. We have grown together.</span></p><h3>Contact Us for Your Requirements</h3><p><strong>Mobile: +91 95 9758 7923</strong></p><p><strong>Phone: +91 80 4149 5757</strong></p><p><strong>Mail: <a href="mailto:info@cairocorps.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">info@cairocorps.com</a></strong></p><p>More Tags: <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Web development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/seo-company-in-bangalore/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEO company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">best web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/ecommerce-solutions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">e-commerce website development company in Bangalore</a></p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/web-design-company-in-nagercoil/">Web Design Company in Nagercoil</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/web-design-company-in-nagercoil/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5235</post-id> </item> <item><title>Difference Between Static and Dynamic Websites</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 08:09:36 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web development company Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website development company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[top web design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web development company in banglore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5214</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Difference Between Static and Dynamic Websites Most of the time when you come across this terms in online or you can hear this words from some of the web designers, you should know the difference between static and dynamic websites so that only you can determine the good solution for your website. Simply we will [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites/">Difference Between Static and Dynamic Websites</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="size-large wp-image-5215 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites-1024x512.png?resize=1024%2C512&#038;ssl=1" alt="Difference between static and dynamic websites, web design company in bangalore, web development company in bangalore" width="1024" height="512" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites.png?w=1024&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites.png?resize=300%2C150&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites.png?resize=768%2C384&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites.png?resize=700%2C350&amp;ssl=1 700w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites.png?resize=600%2C300&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1>Difference Between Static and Dynamic Websites</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">Most of the time when you come across this terms in online or you can hear this words from some of the web designers, you should know the difference between static and dynamic websites so that only you can determine the good solution for your website.<br /> Simply we will explain this from a <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web development company in Bangalore</a>. In Static websites, are those with content that cannot change without developer editing its source code, but Dynamic websites also having same source code we can edit without the help of developers. When we are using static and dynamic websites for our company or organization, it has lots of coding in the backend but the visual is the same for the user. We should know the important purpose of both Static and Dynamic websites.</p><h2>Static Websites</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Static sites are mostly used to portray something about the organization, it is used to show only the information about the organization to the clients. We cannot change the content while the user seeing our site, this kind of static websites are created by HTML and CSS coding with the help of text editors. This website is suitable for unedited organizations.<br /> The static website is always showing the same pages to the clients, even we can add multimedia files like images and videos. However, this static website always welcomes the clients with the same contents and images until we alter the page source code.</p><h2>Dynamic Websites</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">In a dynamic website, we change the content dynamically while the page is running on the client browser. These websites using server-side programming languages like PHP,Asp.net and JSP etc. We can change the contents at the runtime. Dynamic websites using server-side code to handle events, it manages session and cookies, and it will store and retrieve data from the database. <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dynamic_web_page" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Dynamic websites</a> are mainly used for e-commerce websites, online form applications, social networking sites, Regular updating sites etc.<br /> A dynamic website has the capacity of showing different content for different visitors from the same source code. These websites have all kind of media like videos images but whenever the user wants to change that he can change, so it gives a good experience to the user.</p><h2>Uses of Dynamic Websites</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Dynamic websites will give a lot of purposes, for example, the dynamic websites have its content management system (CMS) where you can upload your contents regularly. When we have a blogging website or an e-commerce website then you need to update your content daily, every time we can’t expect the developer to change our contents. Responsive designs are giving more attractive to the dynamic websites. Its suitable for all devices.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Everyone Should know the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-2018/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">benefits of responsive web design</a>. Dynamic websites are suitable for SEO capability, so we can get good traffic and valuable customers for our business. This kind of dynamic websites is very much useful to when we are doing digital marketing. We can easily create landing pages while doing digital marketing.</p><h2>The Advantage of Digital Marketing</h2><p>In this competitive world, we should stand among other with good websites. If we are looking for customers from our websites we should do digital marketing like SEO, Google ads, Social media presence, and ads and etc. It’s very useful to get valuable customers, that will enlarge your business. Everyone should know why digital marketing is important and <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">advantages of digital marketing</a>.</p><h2>Development steps of Static and Dynamic</h2><p>Static website design process done by HTML and Dynamic sites are created by PHP, <a href="https://www.javascript.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">JavaScript</a>, Asp.net like etc. Also, Dynamic pages are created by Ruby on Rails and some kind of frameworks<br /> • Static sites are load quicker than Dynamic one.<br /> • In static site content changing is a very difficult task, only the developer can change it. But in the dynamic site, we can change the content my own.<br /> • Static sites file extension is like .html or .htm, Dynamic one extension is like .php, .asp, .jsp<br /> • Static sites are creating HTML and CSS, Dynamic sites are creating by using server-side programming languages like PHP, JSP, ASP and etc.<br /> • Static websites are a cheap method and low-cost one, Dynamic websites are little costly than static but it&#8217;s having more useful purposes. Choose dynamic sites if you are updating the content frequently.</p><h2>Which one do we choose?</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Most of the peoples prefer dynamic websites because that have many benefits. Before proceeding this you must choose the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">best web design company in Bangalore</a>. Dynamic websites are reducing ongoing maintenance, reduce the complicity to manage the data and giving SEO support too. In the dynamic site, we can add more future add-ons like data feed and comprehensive site search.<br /> Some of the key point we should keep in our mind while creating dynamic websites, its development cost is high because it requires more complicity coding, another complicity is dynamic website needs high-end web hosting. Who are all in business they should know the Difference between static and dynamic websites.</p><p>More Tags: <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web design company in Bangalore</a></p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites/">Difference Between Static and Dynamic Websites</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/difference-between-static-and-dynamic-websites/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5214</post-id> </item> <item><title>Best Places to Put Contact Forms in Website</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 08:14:39 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web development company in banglore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5203</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Best Places to Put Contact Forms in Website The Contact Forms or Enquiry Forms are called Lead Generation Forms in Business Terms. Because these forms get the details of the user based on the interest the user has in your website or Business Landing Page. The UI/UX makes the user trust the website and makes [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website/">Best Places to Put Contact Forms in Website</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="size-large wp-image-5204 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website-1024x512.png?resize=1024%2C512&#038;ssl=1" alt="best places to put contact forms in website, web design company in Bangalore, web development company in Bangalore" width="1024" height="512" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website.png?w=1024&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website.png?resize=300%2C150&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website.png?resize=768%2C384&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website.png?resize=700%2C350&amp;ssl=1 700w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website.png?resize=600%2C300&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1>Best Places to Put Contact Forms in Website</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">The Contact Forms or Enquiry Forms are called Lead Generation Forms in Business Terms. Because these forms get the details of the user based on the interest the user has in your website or Business <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Landing_page" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Landing Page</a>. The UI/UX makes the user trust the website and makes him/her provide the details those we required to use in our business.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">You need to make sure that You are making it very easy for the user to provide the details by placing contact forms an inappropriate place of the website in order to get more inquiries from the visitors.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">In this article, we will show you up the best places to place the forms on your Website or Landing page</p><h2>Get More Leads from Contact Forms</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">All Websites are evolving through the best practices to put more details about the business to visitors to get the good understanding of it. No matter which industry you belongs to:</p><ul><li>A Business owner needs of customers</li><li>A sales guy require Leads</li><li>An <a href="https://ecommerceguide.com/guides/what-is-ecommerce/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">eCommerce</a> Store looking for maximum sales conversion</li><li>An R&amp;D Team looking for client feedbacks.</li></ul><p style="text-align: justify;">The Website should be able to guide the user to scan through the page to get the idea to help the visitor understand what is about and what you’re looking from them.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">A <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">best web design company</a> practices the A/B testing for the better placement of forms and Contents with a Good Website designer.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">You need to place a call to action buttons or pop-up forms or some sort of things to make your client guide through to fill the forms. The form can be anything as your business needs like newsletter form or inquiry form or even a SignUp Form.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">So, How will you decide what is the best place and practice put the right form in right place? Well, Read on…</p><h2>Here are some good place and practices to place many types of forms:</h2><h3>i) Side Bars</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">One of the easily readable positions of any web page is a sidebar. You can place any form over there with other contents or Menu Links to seek the visitors’ attention. How To articles or Blog posts have a high conversion rate for Sidebars but it’s not only limited to these.</p><p>A Typical Sidebar form looks like below:</p><p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-5205" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/ninja-kick-sidebar-contact-form.jpg?resize=313%2C550&#038;ssl=1" alt="contact forms, web design company in bangalore, web development company in Bangalore" width="313" height="550" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/ninja-kick-sidebar-contact-form.jpg?w=313&amp;ssl=1 313w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/ninja-kick-sidebar-contact-form.jpg?resize=171%2C300&amp;ssl=1 171w" sizes="(max-width: 313px) 100vw, 313px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><p style="text-align: justify;">You can get an advice from a <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web development company in Bangalore</a> for this website enhancement. We focus worldwide from Bangalore.</p><h3>ii) Contact Page</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">The name stands for itself, The Contact Page generally have contact information. By Placing Forms over there, We have a better probability to get the visitor filling the form as the Business contact details also provided explicitly.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">But make sure that you are explaining clearly why the visitors have to give their details in the form. List your contact details including phone number, Address, and Emails.</p><p><img class="size-large wp-image-5206 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website-1024x589.png?resize=1024%2C589&#038;ssl=1" alt="Best Places to put Contact Forms in Website, web development company in Bangalore, web design company in Bangalore" width="1024" height="589" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website.png?resize=1024%2C589&amp;ssl=1 1024w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website.png?resize=300%2C173&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website.png?resize=768%2C442&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website.png?resize=1140%2C656&amp;ssl=1 1140w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website.png?resize=600%2C345&amp;ssl=1 600w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Best-Places-to-put-Contact-Forms-in-Website.png?w=1200&amp;ssl=1 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h3>iii) About Page</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">As you will be detailing about the Organization or Business &#8211; You are already gaining the trust of the visitor. Thus placing the Form here will also yield the results and attention of the visitor. You can place minimal forms such as contact or Newsletter here in the page in midst of the contents or in the sidebar or underneath of the page.</p><h3>iv) Footer</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Always try to place a newsletter form in the footer which is clearly visible to the visitor in all the pages. Forms with very minimal fields can go in the footer. Usually, the users will look for more link about the business in the footer, So if they could get periodic details about your business in the format of a newsletter, They are ready to invest the space for a form.</p><h3>v) Sliding bars and Pop-Ups</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">The attention-seeking pop-ups or actionable items are always a good place to put a Form by making the visitor to enjoy more benefits like offers or secrets or tips. The visitors will be eager to receive these by filling a form if your actionable item is eye catch or having better Look and feel.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">All these methods will surely help you to maximize lead generation. Please comment your thoughts and more findings. We will update our article if required. Thanks!</p><p style="text-align: justify;">If you need any help on any Web User Experience, Contact Us today. CairoCorps is committed to providing the best service to satisfy clients. It’s one of the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">best web design company in Bangalore</a>.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">And don’t forget, if you like this article, then please follow us on Facebook and Twitter.</p><p><strong>More Tags: </strong><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website design company in Bangalore</a></p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website/">Best Places to Put Contact Forms in Website</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/best-places-to-put-contact-forms-in-website/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5203</post-id> </item> <item><title>How to Sell a Website to a Client in 2018</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/how-to-sell-a-website-to-a-client/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/how-to-sell-a-website-to-a-client/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 05:10:23 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web development company Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website designers in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[top web design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web development company in banglore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website developers in bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5195</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>How to Sell a Website to a Client in 2018 You make websites; and if you also sell web design services to our clients, you are probably doing a good job. The issue is, however, being able to make good websites doesn’t always mean you can sell your web design services to the clients in [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/how-to-sell-a-website-to-a-client/">How to Sell a Website to a Client in 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-5196 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/How-to-Sell-a-Website-to-a-Client.png?resize=900%2C350&#038;ssl=1" alt="How to Sell a Website to a Client" width="900" height="350" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/How-to-Sell-a-Website-to-a-Client.png?w=900&amp;ssl=1 900w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/How-to-Sell-a-Website-to-a-Client.png?resize=300%2C117&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/How-to-Sell-a-Website-to-a-Client.png?resize=768%2C299&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/How-to-Sell-a-Website-to-a-Client.png?resize=600%2C233&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1>How to Sell a Website to a Client in 2018</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">You make websites; and if you also sell web design services to our clients, you are probably doing a good job. The issue is, however, being able to make good websites doesn’t always mean you can sell your web design services to the clients in a perfect way or either you are a good marketing person also. Here I discuss How to Sell a Website to a Client in 2018.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">When you sell web design services for a normal human being, your designs become more than an artful effort, they suddenly become a product that you should sell, produce, and deliver. It’s a hard transition for some designers, but it is one you must make if you want to persist as a self-governing expert.</p><h2>Is it so hard to sell web design services to your client?</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Selling anything online can be a hurdle these days. With so many web designers everywhere, it’s hard to stand out among the crowds. The obstacle is, While there is a lot of opportunity for the largest volume, with so many people trying to sell the same thing, the struggle is terrifying.<br /> The basis of this is, the web designers or the web designing companies has it tough nowadays. Web design services are especially challenging because an expanding number of businesses require websites, technology has created it easy for them to do it themselves. On the other hand, those who want more customized solutions usually should select a company or individual who can understand their concept and idea in a healthy way and execute it up to their expectations. That means they should select a dedicated team for them.</p><h2>Hints for selling web design services to your clients:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Selling anything is about building connections. Focus on these tips to enhance the connections you have with good clients and market more of your web design services.</p><h3>1. Market the benefits of a website</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">A pretty website is a form of creativity. Sadly, most businesses are not interested in buying creativity. They are only focusing on outcomes in order on the returns on their investment and enhanced customer&#8217;s comfort. Your website should resolve all the issues or satisfy all their requirements.<br /> When selling your website to your client. Show your client how you can help them make more money. As the conclusion, that is what they want to hear.<br /> sometimes, a website is not affordable for smaller companies, so it is necessary to describe what is the benefits of a website for the business and <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">advantages of digital marketing</a> are numerous so in future without the website you will not do digital marketing. Nowadays most of the people are familiar with websites, and the can understand that they need it and without expectation of their costs.</p><h3>2. Be genuine</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">In this world market, it is essential to do something that makes you and your services will sustain like a unique service among all the market availabilities. One of the powerful tools to achieve this is by being genuine and reliable to your clients.<br /> Genuinity makes it easier for your clients to connect with you, results in a good relationship. These relationships will leads to sell web design services without even using any marketing skills.</p><h3>3. Educate your clients about your services</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Mainly if you work with small or medium businesses, there will be a situation for learning your clients. Many of them are not aware of what they can do with a well-designed website but you can teach them and sell your website to the client in a better way.<br /> You can show to your clients; some of the things they can perform with a professionally built website.<br /> The next important way to educate them by comparing their business with their competitors beside educate <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">how to choose the best web design company</a>. If you ready to describe or educate the diversity to a potential client, it always works in your boon – particularly if you are good at it.</p><h3>4. Product Creation</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Although you sell web design services, most of the potential clients will prefer to buy products. So you have to sell them like a product to sell the website to clients in a better way.<br /> Some planning need to build a product out of your services. You should plan to analyze your services and experience to calculate the time taken for a task to complete. select no of services and sell them as packages for a good marketing way. Change it whatever you can.<br /> It may be detached but at last; it may be useful for our clients. Converting products as packages will lead to results an enhanced performance, and stops you from catching on projects that are not in your list of interests.<br /> Products can be created with the consideration of all requirement. you should finalize the area that you should concentrate by differentiating it as each industry or services that they looking for. The main thing you should concentrate that, when you sell a website to a customer you should concentrate more on each package instead of all in one solution as one website creation.</p><h4>Below listed some examples for the products:</h4><ul><li>Restaurant site</li><li>Builders site</li><li>Real Estate site</li><li>Health care site</li><li>Education site</li><li>E-commerce site</li><li>Astrologers site</li><li>Financial Site</li><li>Informatory site</li></ul><h3>5. Connections for your communications</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Connections are more important in this marketing process. If you wanted to sell a website to your customer then you should build a strong networking among your market; Because a business is more than selling or marketing a product /services. Business is the art of delivering an excellent product or services as per customers expectations.<br /> The time when you are searching for a new client you should start with your local community. Start with an email campaign to the local business holders and try to join local business organizations too for explaining more about your products and services. Like this small initiatives, you can sell your website to the customers who are looking for it or at least they will get aware of your services.<br /> you should avoid the traditional selling methods when it comes to selling a website to a client. We can avoid email marketing, cold calling and instead of we can create a personal connection with each customer. This will leads to the long-term relationship.</p><h3>6. Provide offers with web design</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">You are a <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web development company in Bangalore</a> although you can provide some offers with the web design services. Don&#8217;t worry about this; you can collaborate some other companies or freelancers to providing this small offer on your services.</p><h4>Listed few of the services below:</h4><ul><li><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-2018/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Responsive</a> to all devices</li><li>SEO compatible</li><li>Website management and hosting</li><li>Website customer service</li><li>Internet marketing services</li><li>Graphic design</li><li>Social media profile creation</li></ul><p style="text-align: justify;">The above-listed services will show that you are more concentrating on your client&#8217;s success in their business. If they are the startup you can explain the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website design process for startup</a>.</p><h3>Before you start selling…</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Using the steps that mentioned above you can show your uniqueness in this well-competitive world, but your company should have the talent to showcase your identity too. You should have a good portfolio to showcase to your clients with your website also; case studies also will help in this. This struggling will be there until you became an established website developer; Till this, you should need some extraordinary portfolio to show your clients to take the decision that they should work with you or they need a help to grow in their business. These are the things How to Sell a Website to a Client in 2018.</p><h2>CairoCorps Consulting &#8211; A web development company in Bangalore</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">We are a web design company based in Bangalore (Silicon Valley of India) and we are offering interactive web design services to startup, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Small_business" target="_blank" rel="noopener">small enterprises</a>, NGOs and etc&#8230;CairoCorps is holding enough team to develop the attractive and user-friendly website to all business. For packages and prices contact us immediately&#8230;</p><p>More Tags: <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/seo-company-in-bangalore/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEO company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/ecommerce-solutions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">e-commerce website development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/mobile-application-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing company in Bangalore</a></p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/how-to-sell-a-website-to-a-client/">How to Sell a Website to a Client in 2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/how-to-sell-a-website-to-a-client/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5195</post-id> </item> <item><title>Why Digital Marketing is Important in 2018?</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 07:27:48 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO agency in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[seo company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5185</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Why digital marketing is important in 2018? Marketing is the backbone of every business in the world without marketing you never succeed in your respective business. Marketing is how you sell a product when customers need the explanation of awesome products. The present reality is that promoting sales at the intersection of the business, therefore, [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/">Why Digital Marketing is Important in 2018?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="wp-image-5186 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important.png?resize=594%2C334&#038;ssl=1" alt="why digital marketing is important" width="594" height="334" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 594px) 100vw, 594px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1 style="text-align: left;">Why digital marketing is important in 2018?</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">Marketing is the backbone of every business in the world without marketing you never succeed in your respective business. Marketing is how you sell a product when customers need the explanation of awesome products. The present reality is that promoting sales at the intersection of the business, therefore, the client – the good arbiter of the self-interests of the business and therefore the wants of the customer. Current days have two main marketing that includes online marketing and digital marketing. Here I write elaborately why digital marketing important in 2018. Once you read you will get more about digital marketing.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">What is Digital Marketing</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Promoting products or services or brands through several forms of digital technology that is digital marketing. For example, advertising mediums that might be used as part of the digital marketing strategy of a business could include promotional endeavors performed through the internet, social media, mobile phones, and computerized billboards. Similar to any form of marketing, the goal of digital marketing is to promote and sell a product or service. Further, the purpose of digital marketing is to connect a business or company with its target audience through several digital marketing strategies such as Search Engine Optimization(SEO), Pay Per Click(PPC), Social Media Marketing(SMM), Social Media Optimization(SMO), Newsletter Campaign and bulk SMS, and etc&#8230;</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Why digital marketing is important</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Digital marketing is most important marketing in the world because it is not only a quickly growing force in the contemporary marketing playing area but also it is set to be the future of every business, and it appears probable that digital marketing will quickly replace all types of offline marketing forms altogether because <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">advantages of digital marketing</a> is huge. While earlier generations will no doubt regret the decease of paper-based newspapers, books, communication methods, and conventional TV advertisements and radio broadcasts, those who have grown up with the internet penetration and mobile phones penetration are already covering the bright new world of digital marketing. The realities are that digital marketing methods of transmission and marketing are so fast besides cost-effective, more adaptable, efficient and modernized, so it is possibly unsurprising that once the new technology became accessible we started quickly moving into the new technology then only digital marketing so important for every business.</p><p><img class="wp-image-5187 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018.png?resize=597%2C336&#038;ssl=1" alt="" width="597" height="336" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 597px) 100vw, 597px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2>7 Important of Digital Marketing</h2><p>Here you can read seven reasons being to why digital marketing is important in 2018.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">1. The whole World Well Connected With Internet</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Why digital marketing is booming, well the whole world there are several factors associated or responsible for digital marketing growth. Besides one of the importance of digital marketing is the whole world well connected to the internet because of the cheap internet and mobile users increased. We have been seeing the difference in communication since the arrival of the internet. The Internet has undoubtedly changed the way of purchasing and communicating with the people. Everything has become the fast-paced and getting people more laziness since whatever you want just gives up at your doorstep with just one click. These are the reason for digital marketing is booming and the importance of digital marketing in 2018 and upcoming years.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">2. Customers are Online</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">People believe online as a way to cut costs and cut time. E-commerce shops assist customers of travel time and retailers of storefront costs so buyers are roaming always the internet to buy something. People rarely consider the costs that online shopping adds to their transaction. The distance between the buyer and seller adds risks to the customers plate. If youre part of an E-commerce business, the takeaway is this risks. In lightweight of this, associate degree service an e-commerce merchant will offer to ease the psychological feature prices of looking online will increase the customer’s perceived price of the merchandise. Today people are roaming the internet and customers are always online that is why digital marketing is important in 2018.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">3. Competitors are Online</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Competitors were gone beyond you in business Its sign of digital marketing adoption. Literally, most of the businesses are using digital marketing. Each year more and more businesses give up offline marketing methods and focus on SEO, Google Adwords or social media spending large money on these marketing. This is the explanation for why the market gets progressively competitive and large players to get prior to very little firms. As little business on the market, you can&#8217;t vie with them, however, there&#8217;s one thing you&#8217;ll do. you&#8217;ll use Google Alerts tool to observe your competitors. This tool can enable you to trace your competitors&#8217; product and selling methods in order that you&#8217;ll learn one thing from them and improve your own business strategy. Competitors are online so immediately hunt a best digital marketing company.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">4. Cost-effective Marketing</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">One of the importance of digital marketing is more cost-effective while comparing other offline marketing. This is especially essential for startups and small business. Digital marketing is savvier than offline marketing. This is particularly vital for independent companies as they don&#8217;t have numerous assets or a considerable measure of capital. New media can furnish you with a less expensive and more compelling publicizing digital marketing company channel. In digital marketing has many types of marketing according to your budget you can choose the suitable strategies. <img class="alignnone wp-image-5188 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/Feature_Image_Mobile_Device_Management_BYOD_Evolution.jpg?resize=630%2C295&#038;ssl=1" alt="why digital marketing is important" width="630" height="295" srcset="https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/Feature_Image_Mobile_Device_Management_BYOD_Evolution.jpg?w=600&amp;ssl=1 600w, https://i1.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/Feature_Image_Mobile_Device_Management_BYOD_Evolution.jpg?resize=300%2C141&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 630px) 100vw, 630px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h3 style="text-align: left;">5. Cater to the Mobile Consumer</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">No doubt, Digital marketing has evolved such a lot that mobile devices are not any longer thought-about mere alternatives to private computers or laptops. Without any doubt, with the fast expansion of smartphones, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mobile_marketing" target="_blank" rel="noopener">mobile marketing</a> is the most contemporary way of data dispersal that is also today’s basic correspondence channel. Smartphones have transformed into the main part of our life that most of the grown-ups in India dependably have their mobile devices within their reaching distance. The greatest gathering of customers is using their cell phones day by day, so it&#8217;s basic that you utilize a marketing arrangement that objectives these mobile gadgets suitably.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">6. Highly Adaptable Marketing</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Importance of digital marketing is changing is that it needs digital marketers to be equally willing to vary and adapt. Flexibility, therefore, is a necessary quality during a digital promoting skilled, as a result of you usually ought to be ready to adopt new practices, update your ability set and knowledge domain, sustain with business best practices, and keep current with the newest technologies and trends. an excellent example of however things area unit perpetually dynamic in digital promoting is that the Google formula. The formula is often being updated, and each time they unharness a replacement version, it changes the means digital marketers and <a href="https://moz.com/learn/seo/what-is-seo" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEO</a> specialists approach their craft.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">7. Most of the People Shopping Online</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">A recent research has exposed that over 120 million Indian people are expected to buy the products or services through online this year. In the previous year of study exposed that as many as 108 million consumers did online shopping on mobile phones. Mobile phones are becoming the favored choice of device for e-commerce businesses. The research also highlighted a flood in the number of customers shopping on smartphones across India and the world with tier II and III cities are increasing trends.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Best Digital Marketing Company in Bangalore</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">CairoCorps Consulting is one of a best <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing company in Bangalore</a> who takes care of clients and feel their pain provide the best digital marketing of their business put their business at top of the competition despite any industry. The organization is also holding professional experts on the latest technologies of digital marketing with very comprehensive solutions.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>You have any suggestion about this blog let us know through comments&#8230;</strong></p><p><strong>More Tags:</strong> <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEO agency in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/interactive-web-solution/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing services in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/ecommerce-solutions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">e-commerce development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/mobile-application-development/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">e-commerce development company in Bangalore</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: left;"><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/">Why Digital Marketing is Important in 2018?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/why-digital-marketing-is-important-in-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5185</post-id> </item> <item><title>Benefits of Responsive Web Design-2018</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 11:42:27 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web designers in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web development company Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website design companies in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website designers in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website development company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[list of web development companies in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[responsive web design bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[responsive web design company bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[responsive web design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[top web design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design services in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web development services bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website designers in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website developers in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5162</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>Benefits of Responsive Web Design-2018 We are lived among the peoples either they are educated or illiterate. In this modern world every one looking for the change even if they don&#8217;t know about the technology. Previous days if anyone getting any doubts they may get to know either from someone or from books. But nowadays [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-2018/">Benefits of Responsive Web Design-2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class=" wp-image-5163 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-1.png?resize=649%2C365&#038;ssl=1" alt="benefits of responsive web design, web design company in bangalore" width="649" height="365" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-1.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-1.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 649px) 100vw, 649px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1>Benefits of Responsive Web Design-2018</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">We are lived among the peoples either they are educated or illiterate. In this modern world every one looking for the change even if they don&#8217;t know about the technology. Previous days if anyone getting any doubts they may get to know either from someone or from books. But nowadays they have an easy way to know everything by the using of Google. Now everyone using google for getting knowledge, images, videos and etc. Now it&#8217;s become a part of life.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Many businesses running by using the internet and that makes them as multi-millionaire like Amazon, Flipkart, and more e-commerce businesses. Moreover, most of the businesses only depending on the internet. So as a business person we should show our presence in front of the world. How can we do that? I&#8217;ll give you the solution, try to <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">choose the best web design company</a> who give the best website for affordable price. After that, you just portray who you are and what you are going to selling. The world looking for an easy way that makes them more comfortable without any hurdles.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Website design companies having more types of websites like static, dynamic, e-Commerce and etc. You just Portray who you just pick static one. If you going to do regular updates ill suggest you take dynamic one. You have more products that you are going to sell in online means don’t hesitate to take the e-Commerce website. Are you a writer just pick the blogging website. Similarly, we have a lot of choices before choosing yours try to consult with a good <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website development company</a>. They will give proper guidance about it.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Most important things on your website to be compatible with all devices, In olden days websites, are not useful for anything now it’s a business market for enlarging your business. So I would suggest doing its responsive. why I&#8217;m saying like that and what is the use of that? Below I&#8217;ll say you all the benefits and its making process.</p><p><img class="wp-image-5164 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/benefits-of-responsive-web-design.png?resize=670%2C377&#038;ssl=1" alt="advantages of responsive web design, web design company in bangalore" width="670" height="377" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/benefits-of-responsive-web-design.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/benefits-of-responsive-web-design.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 670px) 100vw, 670px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: left;">History of Responsive Website Design</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Before proceeding how it will make I would like to say its history, The first website designed to adapt its layout based on the width of the browser is Audi.com. They are the one who created the device-adaptive website. It was launched in 2001. After 2011 the developer Ethan Marcotte use the same type of technology and phase it <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Responsive_web_design" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Responsive Web Design</a>, Marcotte wrote a book on the subject in 2011 simply titled “Responsive Web Design.”</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">8-Important Benefits of Responsive Web Design</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Nowadays everyone has a mobile in their hand, They were getting everything from there. So as a business people we should satisfy our customers by providing good looking and compatible websites for all device, Its more useful to convert them as our customer. The first approach is more important than anything. So Responsive websites are more important for recent days.</p><p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-5165 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/eda.jpg?resize=560%2C315&#038;ssl=1" alt="" width="560" height="315" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/eda.jpg?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/eda.jpg?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 560px) 100vw, 560px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h3>1. Mobile Users Increased</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">By the statics, the mobile users are increased after 2014. So they mobile traffic is increased. Most of the peoples are searching in mobile, Therefore the companies to have websites and that should adaptable for all devices. If you created a website in the responsive way its suitable for Mobile, Tablets and all types of screens. While some companies are creating the separate version for their mobile view customers.</p><h3>2. Faster and low cost</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Create one Responsive website considerable less time and low cost than making a stand-alone mobile application and a standard desktop website. Initial develop cost only the investment of developing a responsive website. No more maintenance cost and special configuration cost.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">3. Maintenance Cost is low</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Maintaining a separate mobile site need to test and support. In contrast, the responsive use standardizing testing methods to ensure optimal layout on every screen. If we have two type of desktop and mobile sites mean, we concentrate on two type of content strategies and two administrative interfaces and two different designing teams. Responsive designs take less time and low cost for maintaining the site.</p><h3>4.Fast Loading Web pages</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Mobile users are having short-term attention spans. Studies say that the mobile users tend to abandon web pages that take longer than three seconds to finish loading. So as a provider we should give easy and fast loading web pages. When we going to responsive design it gives faster loading for mobiles and other devices. Its using modern performance techniques such as caching and image display will help to improve your web pages loading speed.</p><p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-5166 aligncenter" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/advantages-of-responsive-web-design.png?resize=900%2C300&#038;ssl=1" alt="benefits of responsive web design, web design company in bangalore" width="900" height="300" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/advantages-of-responsive-web-design.png?w=900&amp;ssl=1 900w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/advantages-of-responsive-web-design.png?resize=300%2C100&amp;ssl=1 300w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/advantages-of-responsive-web-design.png?resize=768%2C256&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/advantages-of-responsive-web-design.png?resize=600%2C200&amp;ssl=1 600w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h3>5. Reduce Bouncing Rate</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">If you know about Search Engine Optimization definitely have an idea about the bouncing rate. A responsive and optimized mobile site gives a much better user experience for the customers. Therefore, if the customer like our page they will stick around for a long period of time and explore more pages of our site. Alternatively, if our site isn’t responsive it is much harder to keep the customers on our website and at the end, the bouncing rate will increase.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">6. Conversion Rate will Increase</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Creating consisting user experience across all device is key to converting new customers. Having a single secure website that looks professional on all platforms make the user less likely to get frustrated or turn to a competitor.</p><h3>7. Getting Easy Analytics</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">You can easily find out the way how the users come and where they go to your site. It helps us to improve our website and its pages. In responsive design, we will give the good experience to the customers and they are spending much time in our site. We have a single site so it&#8217;s not much harder to analyze your site. <a href="https://analytics.google.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Google Analytics</a> and similar tools now cater to the responsive website by condense tracking and analytics into a single report so that you can find how your contents are performing on different devices.</p><h3 style="text-align: left;">8.Successful in SEO</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">In responsive websites every content is optimized clearly, it will give full satisfaction to the visitor, So the bouncing rate is improving day by day, it gives good google ranking. The contents are updated in a single admin and it will reflect all devices. Stronger backlinks and better bounce rates translate into higher search rankings, but there’s an extra SEO benefit for mobile-optimized sites. This is crucial because of SEO one digital marketing strategy. <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">Advantages of digital marketing</a> are huge.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Those are the advantages of a responsive web design. This is essential for any kind of website. Responsive web design provides the best experience for your website visitors. If you desire to be on top you have to make a responsive website for your business. As you can get it is beneficial for you to have a responsive web design presently and for the future.</p><h2 style="text-align: left;">Bespoke Responsive Web Design Company in Bangalore</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">CairoCorps is one of the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/">best web design companies in Bangalore</a> besides we provide comprehensive digital marketing services such as SEO, PPC, SMM, SMO, etc&#8230; If you have any inquiries about responsive web design please let us know. You&#8217;re needed your website redesigned responsively contact us now!</p><p><strong>More Tags: </strong><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SEO agency in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">digital marketing company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/interactive-web-solution/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">website development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/ecommerce-solutions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">e-commerce developers Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/mobile-application-development/">mobile application development company in Bangalore</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-2018/">Benefits of Responsive Web Design-2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/benefits-of-responsive-web-design-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5162</post-id> </item> <item><title>10 steps website design processes for startup -2018</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 08:14:49 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Website]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best web development company Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[best website design companies in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[top web design company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design services in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5149</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>10 Steps Website Design Processes for Startup-2018 The website is crucial for every business because marketing in business is an essential thing while doing marketing every one should move according to the latest and influenced marketing. Nowadays every one knew digital marketing better than traditional marketing because of internet penetration across global besides having lots [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018/">10 steps website design processes for startup -2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="wp-image-5150 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/10-steps-website-design-processes-for-startup-2018.png?resize=601%2C338&#038;ssl=1" alt="10 steps website design processes for startup -2018, web design company in bangalore" width="601" height="338" srcset="https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/10-steps-website-design-processes-for-startup-2018.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i2.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/10-steps-website-design-processes-for-startup-2018.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 601px) 100vw, 601px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1><strong><span style="font-size: x-large;">10 Steps Website Design Processes for Startup-2018</span></strong></h1><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The website is crucial for every business because marketing in business is an essential thing while doing marketing every one should move according to the latest and influenced marketing. Nowadays every one knew digital marketing better than traditional marketing because of internet penetration across global besides having lots of <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/">advantages of digital marketing</a>. The website is one of the biggest tools of the digital marketing process. web design is a little tough task. You are constantly developing your design until you reach the viewpoint. The web design’s progress depends on how well you connect elements such as lines, fonts, colors, images, design, and textures to describe a company’s mission and vision. The attention is extremely essential during each part of the process of website design. You want to get into website design for your startup literally you have many doubts Where do I start? How do I start? How can I <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/">choose the best web design company</a>? Here I explain the details of the 10 steps website design process for startups-2018.</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Your startup needs a website which includes professional and eye-catchy and this can be a tricky perspective for your website design to complete. Luckily there are 10 steps website design process you can follow on which can assist the website design process move easily. You have taken the strong step to commence your own startups business, fine now let&#8217;s take a little effort to design the website for your startups.</span></p><p style="text-align: center;"><img class="alignnone wp-image-5151" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/website-design-processes-for-startup.png?resize=602%2C338&#038;ssl=1" alt="website design processes for startup -2018, website development company in bangalore" width="602" height="338" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/website-design-processes-for-startup.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/website-design-processes-for-startup.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Keep Design Simple</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The most common suggestion from my client&#8217;s side about their website design is &#8216;makes it simple and unique&#8217;. The website shows the brand name of your startup so it must impress the guests. A simple website without unnecessary distractions is less overwhelming, particularly for first-time guests. By a less intricate design, users will be able to keep their focus on the content they are looking for. Presently be sure to make the information on your site clear and short to engage their attention; because a really effective website design doesn’t just look great, it also helps the content efficiently so make simple your websites.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Content Creation</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Content is always the king of your website can seldom be the stimulating part of your website. It requires to attract the visitors and convey the right kind of information at the top level so guests actually read it instead of jumping on to the other website. When you write content, imagine twice about it from an advertising viewpoint. Besides to content, you also need to add attractive images and graphics are commonly used to increase the text content or seldom even replace it. Earning the pages professional viewing is especially significant as visual influence and attraction is a key part of any website. The website is an area where you should use content, images, videos, graphics, infographics and unless you are very good at generating these things, you might need to hunt a <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/">web design company</a> to assist you.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Page Load Time</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">When you design a website page loading speed is crucial because guests have no patience for your websites with lower load speeds performance.A study said, touching half of the web users anticipate the website to load in 2 seconds or less. If it isn’t loaded within 3 seconds, users lead to abandoning the respective website. That indicates you’re not only losing your current guests and reducing conversion rates, though you run the risk of your website losing traffic from those customers who may have referred your website to others. With that in mind, let’s try to get the speedy website for your startup and optimize your website for the best potential performance.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Make User-Friendly</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">User-friendly website developing is the art of making your website and easy to use. Knowing your customer’s online presence provides you insight into what does and what doesn&#8217;t. The mystery lies in proper preparation and thorough experiment behind the user-friendly website. Largest established companies have a step in their project progress especially the website designed to identify and eliminate possible user-friendly issues. It typically has no website design elements or color; preferably it concentrates on something. The sole focus is on content, structure, flow, and functionality without other visuals to distract the eye. so try to design the user-friendly website for your startup.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Clear Call to Action</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The purpose of designing an e-commerce website or any website is to obtain it helpful for users to buy products and services or other purposes. A simplistic approach of encouraging progress is by including Clear Call to Action(CTA) in the website such as buttons, images, and links followed by an actionable text that demonstrates to the guests the outcome of their actions. If your website has been receiving a lot of traffic, but the conversion rate does not resemble to be good enough, among the many possible reasons, there often is the absence of well-designed and strategically located CTAs. Placing of CTAs is very important for your website so the consultation of the website designer keep it proper.</span></p><p><img class=" wp-image-5152 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018.png?resize=570%2C321&#038;ssl=1" alt="website design processes for startup -2018, website design services in bangalore" width="570" height="321" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 570px) 100vw, 570px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Case Studies</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Case studies are a marketing hook of your startup. Companies use them to show how their product or service has been completed successfully and delivered to customers. Rather than just talking about a product or services, case studies empower businesses to show how their product or services can be used. An efficient case study will incorporate similar elements of your startup while designing website placed correct place or arrange separate page for the case study in your website.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Links to Social Pages</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Social media profiles work properly with your startup website to improve your online business of startup. Applying links on your website plays a vital role in its search engine rankings. Google will automatically connect your social media pages with your company when recognizing the links on your website. There is the huge number of ways to combine your social media presence on your startup website. Have many advantages to attaching social media such as <a href="https://www.facebook.com/CairoCorps/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://plus.google.com/+CairoCorpsConsulting">Google+</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/cairocorps/" class="broken_link">LinkedIn</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/cairocorps/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://in.pinterest.com/cairocorps/">Pinterest</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/CairoCorps">Twitter</a> and etc to your website. The help of a website builder to add social media pages to your website its an easy process.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Make the Website Responsive</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Today most of the people spend the time on browsing your favorite websites or social media or ordering things through the mobile phone. Most of the people owned the smartphone, it is important that your website looks good and works well on all devices. That is why all websites must fit responsive web design. Responsive web design is the practice of building a website suitable to run on every device and every screen size, no matter how large or small, mobile or desktop. Responsive web design is concentrated around providing an intuitive and satisfying user experience for everyone regardless of the device they use to access your website so must design the responsive website for your startup.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>Add Some Fun</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The main goal of all projects that we need them to make an impression on people. We want the websites that we create to be remarkable. A fun activity is usually an enjoyable one and an enjoyable experience is usually an interesting thing. Hence, it attains to mind that one of the ways to create a memorable experience is to make it a fun experience. we take a look at how adding a little fun into the mix can help us produce more engaging and expectedly more successful so add some fun to your website.</span></p><h2 style="text-align: left;"><span style="font-size: x-large;"><b>SEO Friendly</b></span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Most of the people know how much important of Search Engine Optimization(SEO) when comes on online presence. Although there is no getting ranking without satisfying the Google bot. This means is developing an SEO plan that satisfies the requirements of your brand and consumers. the step is creating an SEO compliance website. If the website you have isn’t optimized, then it’ll fight to get to the top of the search engine page results. Hold in your mind that users seldom go beyond the first page of search engines. So get it as SEO friendly websites.</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong><span style="font-size: medium;">Do you have the suggestion other hints and best exercises for website design processes for startup-2018? Comment here&#8230;</span></strong></p><p><strong>More Tags: </strong><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/interactive-web-solution/">Website Development Company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/ecommerce-solutions/">ecommerce website design in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/mobile-application-development/">mobile application development company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/">best digital marketing services in bangalore</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018/">10 steps website design processes for startup -2018</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/website-design-processes-for-startup-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5149</post-id> </item> </channel> </rss>