<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
><channel><title>advantages of digital marketing &#8211; CairoCorps Consulting</title> <atom:link href="https://cairocorps.com/tag/advantages-of-digital-marketing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><link>https://cairocorps.com</link> <description>Creations &#124; Digital Transformations</description> <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 10:31:14 +0000</lastBuildDate> <language>en-US</language> <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod> <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency><image> <url>https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/ccc-logo-1.png?fit=25%2C32&#038;ssl=1</url><title>advantages of digital marketing &#8211; CairoCorps Consulting</title><link>https://cairocorps.com</link> <width>32</width> <height>32</height> </image> <site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">142080933</site> <item><title>How to use landing pages for your business-2018?</title><link>https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/</link> <comments>https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/#respond</comments> <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 10:17:27 +0000</pubDate> <dc:creator><![CDATA[Thomas Julier]]></dc:creator> <category><![CDATA[Digital Marketing]]></category> <category><![CDATA[advantages of digital marketing]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing company in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[digital marketing services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO agency in bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[SEO services in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[web design company in Bangalore]]></category> <category><![CDATA[website development company in Bangalore]]></category><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cairocorps.com/?p=5085</guid> <description><![CDATA[<p>How to use landing pages for your business-2018? When you are planning to create a Google AdWords for your business. The landing page is your key chance to convince the customer to convert &#8211; to buy your products, fill out a form or download a resource. You should have high-quality landing pages to optimize conversion [&#8230;]</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/">How to use landing pages for your business-2018?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></description> <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="wp-image-5086 aligncenter" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/how-to-use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=671%2C377&#038;ssl=1" alt="Use landing pages for business, digital marketing company in bangalore" width="671" height="377" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/how-to-use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?w=560&amp;ssl=1 560w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/how-to-use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=300%2C169&amp;ssl=1 300w" sizes="(max-width: 671px) 100vw, 671px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h1 style="text-align: justify;">How to use landing pages for your business-2018?</h1><p style="text-align: justify;">When you are planning to create a Google AdWords for your business. The landing page is your key chance to convince the customer to convert &#8211; to buy your products, fill out a form or download a resource. You should have high-quality landing pages to optimize conversion rates, and highly relevant pages will also lower your conversion costs.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Very important quality of an optimized landing page is relevance: Your ad text should be relevant to your keywords, your landing page should be relevant to your Google ad. Landing page with relevant ad text also gets higher quality scores and better ad rankings as a result.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Designing specific landing pages that talk directly to the user&#8217;s search query will have a real impact on your AdWords account and, most importantly, drive more conversions. It’s worth it to devote major time and effort to optimize your AdWords landing pages.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><img class="alignnone wp-image-5087 aligncenter" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business-410x1024.png?resize=652%2C1629&#038;ssl=1" alt="How to use landing pages for your business-2018" width="652" height="1629" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=410%2C1024&amp;ssl=1 410w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=120%2C300&amp;ssl=1 120w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=768%2C1920&amp;ssl=1 768w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?resize=600%2C1500&amp;ssl=1 600w, https://i0.wp.com/cairocorps.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/use-landing-pages-for-your-business.png?w=800&amp;ssl=1 800w" sizes="(max-width: 652px) 100vw, 652px" data-recalc-dims="1" /></p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Create Optimized Landing Pages for Google AdWords</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Creating AdWords landing pages can be a hard task – there’s a lot to take into consideration. Some challenges of creating AdWords landing pages include:</p><h3 style="text-align: justify;">You can’t build landing pages in AdWords:</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">You can&#8217;t have great AdWords ads for your business without solid landing pages, Google won&#8217;t provide landing page assistance within AdWords. So we need to build landing pages separately.</p><h3 style="text-align: justify;">You need outside help to make landing page:</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Designing landing pages generally <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/choose-best-web-design-company-in-bangalore-2018/">choose the best web design company</a> to edit and manage the pages, that web designer to design the pages and a hosting environment. That means major time and money.</p><h3 style="text-align: justify;">Specific requirements for landing pages:</h3><p style="text-align: justify;">The good landing page has many different elements to consider – your landing pages need to be relevant to your keyword and ads in order to earn a good Quality Score. You also need to have conversion tracking properly set up to track what is and is not working.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Follow the steps to improve your landing page experience:</h2><h3 style="text-align: justify;">1. It should be offer relevant, genuine content and Helpful</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Your landing page should contain direct relevant to your google ads text and keywords.</li><li>Provide specific thing while someone clicks on ads. if someone clicks for a particular bike model, they shouldn&#8217;t get all the bikes on the landing page.</li><li>Provide options when a user wants options. if someone’s looking to compare cars, they probably don&#8217;t want to go specific model page. They expect more.</li><li>Give a useful information about whatever you are advertising</li></ul><h3 style="text-align: justify;">2. Increase transparency and loyalty on your website</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Give proper information about your business and what your business does</li><li>Share everything about your product or services before asking visitors to fill out forms</li><li>Show your contact details to find your visitors easily</li><li>Before asking the personal details of the customers, make it clear why you are asking and what you going to do with it</li></ul><h3 style="text-align: justify;">3. Create mobile and computer navigation easy</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Create and design your page well, so people don’t have to hunt around for information.</li><li>Create the best ads that make the peoples order your product.</li><li>when the customers in your landing page don&#8217;t annoy with pop-ups or other features that interfere with their navigation of your site.</li><li>Help the customers to find what they are really expected.</li></ul><h3 style="text-align: justify;">4. Try to Decrease your landing page loading time</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Make it sure your landing page loads quickly once someone clicks on your ad, whether on a computer or mobile device.</li><li>Consider changing your landing page into an Accelerated Mobile Page (AMP).</li><li>Check your site scores on mobile speed, and get quick fixes to improve it.</li></ul><h2 style="text-align: justify;">The Benefits of Using Video on Landing Pages</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">whenever possible you can use the video on your landing pages. It provides a passive engagement medium where visitors can experience your message with very little effort. If you are using video on landing pages can increase conversion by 80%.</p><h3 style="text-align: justify;">Some reasons why video can lift your landing page conversion rates</h3><ul style="text-align: justify;"><li>Landing page&#8217;s video increase the length of time and people stay on your landing page for more time, giving your brand message longer to sink in.</li><li>If you feature yourself or company employees in the video, the trust factor is raised significantly.</li><li>Customers are lazy and prefer to watch vs. read.</li></ul><p style="text-align: justify;">Nowadays the <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/advantages-of-digital-marketing-2018/">advantages of digital marketing</a> are huge so the landing pages are very much useful to attract customers who want to buy your product which one you have shown in google ads. The best landing pages increase the sales and collecting customer’s information. Whenever you are going to run Google AdWords try to create a landing page first. We are here in the market to create good looking and attractive landing page.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Here the Best Digital Marketing Company in Bangalore:</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">We are CairoCorps Consulting Private Limited, One of India’s Best <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/">digital marketing company in Bangalore</a>. We are offering comprehensive services to your business such as landing page creation, running the digital marketing campaign, web design, mobile application development and <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/">SEO services in Bangalore</a>.<br /> <strong>Contact us for landing page creation and to run the digital marketing campaign&#8230;</strong></p><p><strong>More Tags: </strong><a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/digital-consultancy/">SEO agency in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/interactive-web-solution/">Web design company in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/ecommerce-solutions/">eCommerce website design in Bangalore</a> | <a href="https://www.cairocorps.com/mobile-application-development/">Mobile application development company in Bangalore</a></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/">How to use landing pages for your business-2018?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://cairocorps.com">CairoCorps Consulting</a>.</p> ]]></content:encoded> <wfw:commentRss>https://cairocorps.com/how-use-landing-pages-business-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss> <slash:comments>0</slash:comments> <post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">5085</post-id> </item> </channel> </rss>